<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter condition="TITLE=Collaboration Suite;PERM=collaboration_access;ACCESS=CS"
         id="CollaborationSuite" role="TOPIC">
  <title><xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_Collaboration_S"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Module</title>

  <para role="TEXT">The <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
  xpointer="ent_Collaboration_S" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>
  enhances the level of communication between the different actors of
  international trade operations.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Overview</title>

    <para role="TEXT">As a client user you can:</para>

    <itemizedlist role="TEXT">
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Create a list of tasks for any event.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Assign tasks to users in your company, and follow up
        on each of these tasks through reports and a system of automatic
        alerts.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Assign tasks to the company's bank and communicate
        freely with the bank during the preparation phase of a
        transaction.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">There are 3 different types of tasks:</para>

    <itemizedlist role="TEXT">
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Private task - Created, maintained and visible only
        by the user who created it.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Public task - Created by an initial user, it is
        visible to all users of the same company and entity, as the one
        attached to the transaction to which the task is associated.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Assigned task - Created by an initial user and
        assigned to either of the following users/party:</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Another user in the same company: The task is
            only visible to initial user and assignee user, and only these
            users can update its status,</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">An external party, that is, the bank: The task
            is visible to all users in the same entity as the initial user,
            and also to all users in the external company.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">Typically, a task is a query from the current user to
    the bank in order to complete the transaction. Any user with access to a
    task can add a comment to it. These comments are visible to the users
    according to the same rules as the visibility of a task.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">You can define alerts:</para>

    <itemizedlist role="TEXT">
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">While creating a task, you can place a check mark at
        the <guimenu>Notify issuer by email</guimenu> checkbox, for e-mail
        alerts to be sent to you, upon occurrence of any event on this
        task.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">While assigning a task, you can place a check mark
        at the <guimenu>Notify assignee by email</guimenu> checkbox, for
        e-mail alert to be sent to assignee.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">When the <application
    id="ent_Collaboration_S">Collaboration Suite</application> is enabled, a
    task list, initially empty, is created for each transaction managed in
    <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> such as, for instance, the
    initiation, amendments and more. This task list is maintained by the users
    in your company until the transaction is submitted to the bank. From this
    moment, the list of tasks is frozen but the company's users can still
    access the history of the transaction's tasks and comments.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Task</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The client user interface has three different options to
    create tasks. This section describes different ways the task feature can
    be used. Later sections in this chapter describe the Task layout in
    detail.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Collaboration Window (Tasks)</title>

      <para>When you use any function that initiates a transaction like
      <guilabel>Request Letter of Credit</guilabel>, the form that opens has
      <guilabel>Tasks</guilabel> tab beside <guilabel>Section</guilabel> in
      the left side navigation menu. This window is generally referred as the
      <guilabel>Collaboration Window</guilabel>. You can click on it to see
      existing tasks on the transaction or create new task.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">To create a new task on the transaction click
      <guilabel>Create task</guilabel>, fill in a small sub-form, and click
      <guilabel>Create</guilabel>. Assuming you create a task for
      <guisubmenu>LC Initiation</guisubmenu> transaction and save the task.
      You can reopen the form from Drafts tab to see the task in list in
      <guilabel>Collaboration Window</guilabel>. The same view is available to
      any other authorized user.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">To reply to a task, you can add a comment to it by
      clicking <guilabel>Comments</guilabel> by its entry to display all its
      existing comments, and then click <guilabel>Add Comment</guilabel>.
      Users other than the creator cannot edit the task, but can add comments.
      These comments typically form a conversation between the creator of a
      task and the person who carries it out.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Each task has Pending Action on the the task card.
      This is marking task as completed. The user can mark the task as
      completed. Once this is done, the creator can no longer edit the task,
      but people can still add comments to it.</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Collaboration Window</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This section describes the Collaboration Window in
    detail.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In the input form for every event of every product and
    in the transaction's details screen in the history, there is a window for
    managing the tasks associated with the current transaction, where you can
    perform the following:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Define a new task</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Update an existing task</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Add a new comment to a task.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <section role="TEXT">
      <title>Field Details</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The Collaboration Window is termed as <emphasis
      role="bold">Tasks</emphasis>, and lists all assigned and public tasks on
      this transaction. The fields for each task are described below:</para>

      <informaltable role="">
        <tgroup cols="2">
          <colspec colname="c1" colwidth="3.0*"/>

          <colspec colname="c3" colwidth="5.0*"/>

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Field</para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Description</para></entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guimenu>Self, Public,
              Assign</guimenu></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Select the type of task
              you wish to create:</para><itemizedlist>
                  <listitem>
                    <para><type>Self</type>: To be completed by task
                    creator.</para>
                  </listitem>

                  <listitem>
                    <para role="TEXT"><type>Public</type>: Can be done by
                    anyone in your company.</para>
                  </listitem>

                  <listitem>
                    <para role="TEXT"><type>Assign</type>: Assign task to any
                    other user selected entity or bank.</para>
                  </listitem>
                </itemizedlist></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><emphasis role="bold">Title of
              Task</emphasis></entry>

              <entry valign="top">Enter the name to task.</entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Description of Task</guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Enter the details of the
              task.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><emphasis
              role="bold">Entity</emphasis></entry>

              <entry valign="top">Specify the entity, in case the user is
              associated with multiple entities. This entity will be used for
              transaction creation also.</entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Notify issuer by email</guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Place the check mark in
              the checkbox to receive notification by email in case of any
              event occurring on this task.<note>
                  <para>By default, the notification is disable, place the
                  check mark to enable it. This is applicable only for Public
                  and Assign Tasks.</para>
                </note></para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Email</guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Email address to use for
              the above notification.</para><para role="TEXT">Default value is
              your usual email address, if defined in your profile. If not,
              then this field is a mandatory field if the above <guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Notify issuer by email</guilabel> check box is
              checked.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Assign to Bank</guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top">To assign the task to bank</entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><emphasis
              role="bold">Assignee</emphasis></entry>

              <entry valign="top">Name of the user in case the assignment is
              to another user in the entity. Name of the bank in case of task
              is being assigned to bank</entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Notify assignee by
              email</guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Place the check mark in
              the checkbox to send e-mail notification to the assignee.<note>
                  <para>By default, the notification is disable, place the
                  check mark to enable it. This is applicable only for Assign
                  Tasks.</para>
                </note></para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Email</guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Email address of the
              assignee, where e-mail notification will be sent. The field is
              auto-filled with the assignee e-mail address.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para
              role="TEXT"><guibutton>Create</guibutton></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Add the task to the list
              of tasks and close the sub-form. </para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guibutton
              moreinfo="none">Cancel</guibutton></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Close the sub-form without
              adding the task to the list.</para></entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Comments Sub-form</title>

      <para role="TEXT">When you click <emphasis role="bold">
      Comment</emphasis> on a listed task card in the Collaboration Window,
      the following sub-form appears:</para>

      <informaltable role="">
        <tgroup cols="2">
          <colspec colname="c1" colwidth="373*"/>

          <colspec colname="c1" colwidth="627*"/>

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Field</para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Description</para></entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guilabel role="bold">Add
              Comment</guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top">Text box where you can enter the new
              comment.</entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Task Listing</title>

    <para role="TEXT">All the which are associated to event appears as card on
    after the another based on the type of task and assignment</para>

    <para>Task creator: Will be able to see all the task associated to
    event</para>

    <para>Task Assignee: Will be able to see all the tasks assigned to him
    along with public tasks</para>

    <para>Task creator or assignee can mark task as completed by clicking on
    <emphasis role="bold">Pending Action. </emphasis>The same button can be
    used to open completed task also.</para>

    <para/>
  </section>
</chapter>
