<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>Transactions Maintenance Module</title>

  <para role="TEXT">This menu item provides easy access in a single list to the complete
  set of pending transactions initiated by your bank.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Functions</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This module has just one function:</para>

    <variablelist>
      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Transaction
        Maintenance</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Display a list of all pending initiations of export products
          (for instance EL, SR, IC) and pending reportings.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>
    </variablelist>

    <para role="TEXT">Other functions on this Trade Adminisitration menu are described in
    other modules in this book.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Transaction Maintenance</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Display a list of all pending initiations of export products (for
    instance EL, SR, IC) and pending reportings.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">When you select this option, you are presented with a list of all
    reporting transaction records (initiations of EL, SR or IC for instance
    and message to clients) which have been prepared by users at your bank but
    that have not been sent to clients yet for various reasons.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Some of these records may be out of date and will never be sent to a
    client. A bank user with administrator's privilege should delete these
    pending records.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">You can search the list by entering search criteria in the <guilabel
    moreinfo="none">System Id</guilabel>, <guilabel
    moreinfo="none">Company</guilabel>, <emphasis
    role="bold">Currency</emphasis> and/or <guilabel
    moreinfo="none">Product</guilabel> field. (The product can be any product
    in <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />.)</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The product dropdown list is dynamically built with the current
    user's permissions : <literal>trade_admin_xx_access</literal> for
    initiations and <literal>trade_admin_xx_create_reporting</literal> for
    reportingss (xx = product code).</para>

    <para role="TEXT">You can delete multiple records in a single operation directly from
    the list. Each record in the list has a check box which you tick to select
    it. A button at the end of the page deletes all the selected
    records.</para>
  </section>
</chapter>
