<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter condition="TITLE=Administration: Introduction;ACCESS=SY_INTRO"
         role="TOPIC">
  <title>Introduction</title>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Document Overview</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This document describes the <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> front-end for users managing
    the parameters of the system at a customer site. Such users are referred
    to as called Client Administrators in this document, and should not be
    confused with the administrators of the system at a bank site.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The main tasks performed by a Client Administrator are:
    maintenance of their fellow users; adjusting system jurisdiction to suit
    the characteristics of their company; and maintenance of some static data
    shared by all users in the company. All these features are available
    within a single menu in the same page. These functions can be accessed by
    clicking Administration on the action bar on your home page, and selecting
    the required function.</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>Change Profile</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Entity Maintenance</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Jurisdiction Maintenance</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>User Maintenance</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Data Maintenance</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Payee Maintenance</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Alerts Maintenance</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Report Designer</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Audit Queries</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">In each section, an introduction provides an overview of
    the function followed by a detailed description of each option available
    in the module. An option generally corresponds to a sub-menu item.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Terminology</title>

    <para role="TEXT">A <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> system
    is used by two types of organisation: banks, and companies that are
    customers of banks. We refer to the latter as "customers" or "clients" -
    we use these two terms interchangeably.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In addition, we use the term "bank group" to mean a site
    with overriding authority over the system, such as a bank's head
    office.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">A member of the staff of a client or bank is called a
    "user". A user with special administrator privileges is called an
    "administrator".</para>

    <para role="TEXT">A <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> system
    has two different user interfaces: for a user at a client, and for a user
    at a bank or bank group.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Both interfaces have a section called System Features,
    containing functions for administering and configuring the <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> system. The rest of the
    interface contains end-user functions. Which functions are available to a
    given user depends on that user's privileges.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The document that a bank can provide, such as Letters of
    Credit, Standby Letters of Credit, Shipping Guarantees, and so on, are
    referred to as "products".</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The communications between bank and client about an
    individual instance of a product typically consist of a sequences of
    messages. For example, the communications regarding a Letter of Credit
    would consist of the client's initial request, the bank's formal response,
    possibly some free-format messages containing further discussion, and
    possibly some further responses from the bank.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">These individual messages are called "transactions" or
    "transaction events". Those sent by the bank in reply to a client message
    are called "reporting messages" (because the bank is "reporting back" -
    they should not be confused with reports produced using the Report
    Designer module). The whole set of messages concerning one instance of a
    individual product is called a "file" (this represents a "file of
    documents" and should not be confused with the files that can be uploaded
    containing details of a transaction).</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Audience</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This manual is addressed to an administrator at a
    client, and describes the administrator functions in the client user
    interface.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Access Permissions and Administration</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The Administration module is accessible for all
    logged-in company users from the company home page. However, different
    users see different features available, depending on their permissions.
    User permissions can be fully customised, but the following main
    categories of user can be highlighted:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">All trade users are given access to the Change
        Profile module.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Senior trade users are responsible for the Data
        Maintenance module.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">The administrator user is given access to the Change
        Profile, Jurisdiction Maintenance and User Maintenance modules. An
        administrator user may also be given access to the Audit module, in
        order to monitor the actions carried out by via the application by the
        users in the company.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">When the customer company is initially created, an
    administrator user is automatically created with the login ID admin and
    the password password, and granted the default permissions required to
    create and administer additional users.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Administration Terminology</title>

    <para role="TEXT">A Role defines a set of basic permissions (such as
    create LC, add user and so on) that the system checks before giving a user
    access to the corresponding functionalities. Roles therefore define user
    profiles.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The Roles are prepared by the bank to match the company
    jurisdiction organisation: basic roles giving access to all trade
    functionalities can be defined, but fine grained roles can also be tuned
    and prepared if required by the company, in order to match a more complex
    company organisation.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Roles are then granted to users through Administration,
    who are consequently granted the corresponding permissions. Roles are
    therefore the perfect way to set up a particular user profile, and are
    particularly useful to ease and simplify administration tasks.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Date and Amount Formats</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When entering a date in a date field, two formats are
    available. You can enter it in the form DD/MM/YYYY or DDMMYY if your
    locale is for instance France, or in the form MM/DD/YYYY or MMDDYY if your
    locale is for instance the USA.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">For example, entering 180401 produces a display of
    18/04/2001, which in a French locale corresponds to 18th April
    2001.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">When you enter an amount, the system automatically
    formats the value entered according to the currency selected. You can
    either enter the amount using the decimal and group delimiters of your
    locale (for example, respectively [,] and [space] for France, or [.] and
    [,] for Singapore), or directly as a series of digits.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">For example, 123456.00 in a Singaporean locale produces
    a display of 123,456.00 if the currency involved is associated with 2
    decimal places.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Forward and Back Browser Buttons Behaviour</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When you use a Browser's Forward and Back buttons, the
    browser's default behaviour is displayed and <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> doesn't provide any
    customised messages.</para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Browser to Operating System Compatibility Matrix</title>

    <para>The matrix lists browser compatibility with various Operating
    Systems(OS).</para>

    <para>T - Tested</para>

    <para>S - Supported</para>

    <informaltable role="TEXT">
      <tgroup cols="10">
        <colspec colname="c2" colwidth="81*"/>

        <colspec colname="c3" colwidth="101*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="84*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="88*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="98*"/>

        <colspec colname="c9" colwidth="136*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="125*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="116*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="110*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="61*"/>

        <thead>
          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para>Browser Name</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>Applicable Version</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top">Windows 7</entry>

            <entry valign="top">Windows 8.1</entry>

            <entry valign="top">Windows 10</entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>macOS 10.12 (Sierra)</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top">macOS 10.13 (High Sierra)</entry>

            <entry valign="top">macOS 10.14 (Mojave)</entry>

            <entry valign="top">OSX EL Captain</entry>

            <entry valign="top">iOS (iPad)</entry>
          </row>
        </thead>

        <tbody>
          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para>Chrome</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>84/85</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">T</entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>S</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para>Firefox</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>79</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">T</entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>S</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para>Microsoft Edge</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>86</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top">T</entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para/></entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para>Internet Explorer</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>11</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para/></entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para>Safari</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>13</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"><para>S</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para>Safari</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para>12.1</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"><para>S</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>
          </row>
        </tbody>
      </tgroup>
    </informaltable>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Antivirus Scanning Service</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This service provides an interface from <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> to an antivirus scanner of
    your company's choice. You can scan any attachment for viruses before
    uploading it from any transaction screen in <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>. <!--If the antivirus software
    detects a virus, the service will stop the attachment upload and send an
    email notification to your customer relationship manager (CRM). --></para>

    <note>
      <para role="TEXT">This service is enabled by the <xi:include
      href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Administrator.</para>
    </note>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Common Features</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Many options, when selected, display a page that lists
    relevant records. These list pages have some things in common:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">You can enter search criteria in a group of fields
        at the top of the page and click Search, to make the list show only
        records that match these criteria. These fields represent the most
        important fields in the record, as do the columns in the table.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">You can use wildcards in these fields. The wildcard
        character is an asterisk (*). You can use it anywhere in a
        field.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">On pages where the list might be very long - for
        example, if there are many transactions - the list is not displayed
        until you have entered the search criteria and clicked Search. In
        these cases, enter an asterisk in any of the search fields to get the
        entire list.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">If a company has entities defined in its profile,
        then a column and a search criterion field for Entity appear in
        addition to the columns and fields mentioned in the individual
        descriptions below.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">You can click the triangular icons in the heading of
        a column to sort the display on that column in ascending or descending
        order.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">There may be a column where you can click to open
        the individual record for viewing or editing. These are described in
        the sections for the individual options.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Maker-Checker Functionality</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Maker-Checker is a functionality where a transaction has
    to be approved by another user before it can be processed. The transaction
    created by a user (maker), has to be checked and approved by another user
    (checker) with required permissions. This functionality is permissions
    driven and users can be assigned either as a maker or a checker, or both.
    A user can also be assigned as a maker for one transaction and as a
    checker for another transaction. The maker can view details for all
    rejected transactions by using Audit Trail.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Maker-Checker Functionality - Client Admin</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The following is the list of system features functions
      where Maker-Checker is available for Client Admins:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">User: creation, modification, deletion</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Authorisation Matrix: creation, modification,
          deletion</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">User Accounts Access: assignment</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Beneficiary Master: creation, modification,
          deletion is only applicable if the PAB flag is ticked</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Reset Password</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Maker-Checker Functionality - Workflow</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The following is the maker-checker workflow:</para>

      <orderedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">For each function listed, the following additional
          columns are displayed for users with Checker permissions:</para>

          <itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para role="TEXT">Status - The status is used to indicate the
              type of pending transaction for checker to validate (Add, Modify
              and Delete).</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para role="TEXT">Maker User Id - The user Id of the creator of
              the transaction.</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">You can modify a transaction by clicking the Edit
          icon in the right-hand column, view it in non-editable mode by
          clicking the View icon, or delete it by clicking the Delete icon. If
          the checker feature for your user ID is enabled for a particular
          transaction, you can cancel a transaction by clicking on the Cancel
          icon and review by clicking on the Approve or Reject or Return icon.
          Clicking on the Approve or Reject or Return icon displays the
          Approve or Reject or Return form.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">You can review the transaction details and use the
          buttons at the bottom of the page to process further. You can choose
          to approve, reject or return the transaction submitted by maker.
          Refer to the section on Action Buttons for information on button
          functions. You can enter your comments for returning a transaction
          in the Comments (for return) text box.</para>
        </listitem>
      </orderedlist>

      <section role="ITEM">
        <title>Approve or Reject or Return Form - Action Buttons</title>

        <para role="TEXT">The operations that can be performed from this form
        are listed below. They appear at the bottom of the page. For each of
        them, a popup window will appear to confirm the choice.</para>

        <informaltable role="TEXT">
          <tgroup cols="2">
            <colspec colname="c1" colwidth="2.0*"/>

            <colspec colname="c2" colwidth="8.0*"/>

            <thead>
              <row>
                <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Operation</para></entry>

                <entry valign="top"><para
                role="TEXT">Description</para></entry>
              </row>
            </thead>

            <tbody>
              <row>
                <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guibutton>Approve
                </guibutton></para></entry>

                <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Approve the
                transaction.</para></entry>
              </row>

              <row>
                <entry valign="top"><para
                role="TEXT"><guibutton>Reject</guibutton></para></entry>

                <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Reject the
                transaction.</para></entry>
              </row>

              <row>
                <entry valign="top"><para
                role="TEXT"><guibutton>Return</guibutton></para></entry>

                <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Return the transaction
                to the maker with comments. The transaction is displayed with
                the status 'Returned' to the maker, and the maker can correct
                it and submit it again to the checker for a
                review.</para></entry>
              </row>

              <row>
                <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><guibutton>Cancel
                </guibutton></para></entry>

                <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Leave the current page
                and return to the System Features menu.</para></entry>
              </row>
            </tbody>
          </tgroup>
        </informaltable>
      </section>
    </section>
  </section>
</chapter>
