<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<article lang="en">
  <articleinfo>
    <title>
      <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
                  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>
    </title>

    <subtitle>Release Notes</subtitle>

    <releaseinfo>Release <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_portal_version"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/><xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_patch_version"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/></releaseinfo>

    <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_corpauthor"
                xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>

    <legalnotice>
      <title>Copyright</title>

      <para>© <?dbtimestamp format="Y"?> Finastra International Limited, or a
      member of the Finastra group of companies (“Finastra”). All Rights
      Reserved. Confidential - Limited Distribution to Authorized Persons
      Only, pursuant to the terms of the license agreement by which you were
      granted a license from Finastra for the applicable software or services
      and this documentation. Republication or redistribution, in whole or in
      part, of the content of this documentation or any other materials made
      available by Finastra is prohibited without the prior written consent of
      Finastra. The software and documentation are protected as published or
      unpublished works and constitute a trade secret of Finastra
      International Limited, or a member of the Finastra group of companies,
      Head Office: 4 Kingdom Street, Paddington, London W2 6BD, United
      Kingdom.</para>
    </legalnotice>

    <legalnotice>
      <title>Trademarks</title>

      <para>Finastra trademarks used in document and their respective
      sub-brands, and the logos used with some of these marks, are trademarks
      or registered trademarks of Finastra International Limited, or a member
      of the Finastra group of companies (“Finastra”) in various countries
      around the world. All other brand and product names are trademarks,
      registered trademarks, or service marks of their respective owners,
      companies, or organizations, may be registered, and should be treated
      appropriately.</para>
    </legalnotice>

    <legalnotice>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>

      <para>Finastra does not guarantee that any information contained herein
      is and will remain accurate or that use of the information will ensure
      correct and faultless operation of the relevant software, services or
      equipment. This document contains information proprietary to Finastra.
      Finastra does not undertake mathematical research but only applies
      mathematical models recognized within the financial industry. Finastra
      does not guarantee the intrinsic theoretical validity of the calculation
      models used.</para>

      <para>THE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THIS DOCUMENT AND THE GENERAL
      GUIDANCE OF FINASTRA STAFF DOES NOT TAKE THE PLACE OF QUALIFIED
      COMPLIANCE PERSONNEL OR LEGAL COUNSEL WITHIN YOUR INSTITUTION. FINASTRA
      CANNOT RENDER LEGAL, ACCOUNTING OR OTHER PROFESSIONAL SERVICES TO YOUR
      INSTITUTION. THE INFORMATION CONTAINED HEREIN IS GENERAL IN NATURE AND
      DOES NOT CONSTITUTE LEGAL ADVICE OR A LEGAL OPINION. CONSULT YOUR LEGAL
      COUNSEL FOR LEGAL ADVICE SPECIFIC TO YOUR SITUATION OR CIRCUMSTANCES OR
      TO ANSWER ANY LEGAL QUESTIONS. YOUR FINANCIAL INSTITUTION IS SOLELY
      RESPONSIBLE FOR CONFIGURING AND USING THE SOFTWARE OR SERVICES IN A WAY
      THAT MEETS POLICIES, PRACTICES, AND LAWS APPLICABLE TO YOUR INSTITUTION,
      INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION: (1) OPTIONS AND SELECTIONS MADE ON
      PROMPTS; (2) ENTRIES IN THE SOFTWARE PROGRAM; (3) PROGRAM SETUP; AND (4)
      DOCUMENTS PRODUCED BY THE SOFTWARE OR SERVICES. IT IS THE OBLIGATION OF
      THE CUSTOMER TO ENSURE THAT RESPONSIBLE DECISIONS ARE TAKEN WHEN USING
      FINASTRA PRODUCTS. INFORMATION IN THIS DOCUMENT IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE
      WITHOUT NOTICE AND DOES NOT REPRESENT A COMMITMENT ON THE PART OF
      FINASTRA.</para>
    </legalnotice>

    <legalnotice>
      <title>Feedback</title>

      <para>Do you have comments about our guides and online help? Please
      address any comments and questions to your local Finastra
      representative.</para>

      <para>Need more information? Read more about our products at <ulink
      url="http://www.finastra.com">http://www.finastra.com</ulink> or contact
      your local Finastra office at <ulink
      url="http://www.finastra.com/contact">http://www.finastra.com/contact</ulink>.</para>
    </legalnotice>

    <legalnotice>
      <title>Release month and year</title>

      <para>
        <?dbtimestamp format="B Y"?>
      </para>
    </legalnotice>
  </articleinfo>

  <!-- Add the next release patch/drop section here and name it incrementally. For example, Release 5.4.0.1 -->

  <section>
    <title>Introduction</title>

    <para>This document provides release information on Enhancements, Fixed
    Defects, Outstanding Issues, Deployment, Property and Configuration File
    Updates, Interface File Updates, Localization Updates, Build Package
    Updates and Parameter Updates for <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Release
    <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_portal_version1"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>.</para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Enhancement</title>

    <para>The following section provides information on new features and
    enhancements in the release <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_portal_version1"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>.<informaltable>
        <tgroup cols="3">
          <colspec align="center" colwidth="180*"/>

          <colspec colwidth="589*"/>

          <colspec colwidth="231*"/>

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry align="center">Jira Id</entry>

              <entry align="center">Description</entry>

              <entry align="center">Product</entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry>MPS-63704</entry>

              <entry>Data type for sequence index (SEQ_IDX) field is updated
              from 'INT' to 'LONG' which allows a field length up to 18
              digits. Sequence Index field is used in the generation of
              Account Statements.</entry>

              <entry>Cash</entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry>MPSSC-20581</entry>

              <entry>Only those currencies that are associated to a borrower
              in the Facility will be allowed to repricing in Initiate
              Repricing screen.If a currency configuration is not provided for
              a borrower, in such cases the currencies associated to the
              facility will be allowed for the repricing. The related
              properties are provided in loan.properties.</entry>

              <entry>Loan</entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry>MPSSC-20234 &amp; MPSSC-20235</entry>

              <entry><xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
              xpointer="ent_appli"
              xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Loan portal enables
              the banks to filter list of remittance instructions based on the
              payment methods. Only those remittance instructions with payment
              methods configured in database will be displayed to corporate
              users in Loan Initiate Repricing screen. A new configuration is
              added in loan.properties file to enable this enhancement. A new
              parameter (P780) is introduced to control the behavior of this
              feature.</entry>

              <entry>Loan</entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry>MPSSC-20239</entry>

              <entry><xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
              xpointer="ent_appli"
              xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Loan portal enables
              a corporate user to send the net cashflow flag to back office.
              Earlier, FCC net cashflow flag was not sent to back office when
              cashflow checkbox is not checked which resulted in back office
              picking default values configured in back office system.</entry>

              <entry>Loan</entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable></para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Fixed Defects</title>

    <para>This section lists the defects fixed in the current version of
    <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>.</para>

    <informaltable>
      <tgroup cols="7">
        <colspec colwidth="93*"/>

        <colspec align="center" colwidth="110*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="232*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="186*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="137*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="116*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="126*"/>

        <thead>
          <row>
            <entry align="center">SFDC</entry>

            <entry align="center">Jira Id</entry>

            <entry align="center">Summary</entry>

            <entry align="center">Replication Steps</entry>

            <entry align="center">Impact Area</entry>

            <entry align="center">Resolution</entry>

            <entry align="center">Product</entry>
          </row>
        </thead>

        <tbody>
          <row>
            <entry>02281160</entry>

            <entry>MPS-63753</entry>

            <entry>Homepage Line Spacing Issues</entry>

            <entry>1. Login as either bank or customer user 2. Observe that on
            Homepage there are line spacing issues</entry>

            <entry>Impacts Homepage of bank and customer user</entry>

            <entry>Changes done to show proper spacing at Bank and Customer
            Homepage.</entry>

            <entry>FCC Dashboard</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry>01965064</entry>

            <entry>MPS-60181</entry>

            <entry>The state of custom checkboxes is not announced</entry>

            <entry>1. Enable the Accessibility feature 2. Navigate to any
            transaction listing screen with checkboxes 3. Check/Uncheck the
            checkbox of a transaction and verify whether the details of the
            selection is announced</entry>

            <entry>Impacts all screens which list transactions with
            checkboxes.</entry>

            <entry>Added proper description for announcing correct status of
            checkbox in each row of all listing screens.</entry>

            <entry>1. Login to portal as Customer user 2. Navigate to Cash
            Services-&gt;Bulk Services-&gt;Initiation-&gt;From Scratch 3. Add
            more than one Transfers in the Bulk 4. FCC assigns Bulk reference
            to batch and individual references to each transfer transaction.
            5. Submit the Bulk 6. FCC send the Individual Transactions to GPP.
            7. GPP can process the individual transactions successfully 8. FCC
            is not passing Bulk Reference in transfer message and GPP is not
            displaying the same</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry>02282429</entry>

            <entry>MPS-64130</entry>

            <entry>User unable to login to Local Service when the following
            properties are enabled:<programlisting>contentlength.enabled = true
additional.headers = true</programlisting></entry>

            <entry>1. Set the following properties to "True"
            <property>contentlength.enabled</property> and
            <property>additional.headers</property> .2. Login to Local
            Service</entry>

            <entry>Impacts Local Service login</entry>

            <entry>1. Updated the headers as NamedValue 2.Added HttpClient jar
            3. Updated startup.bat</entry>

            <entry>
              <productname>Local Service</productname>
            </entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry>02268470</entry>

            <entry>MPS-63902</entry>

            <entry>All entities are displayed in report execution for a user
            who is assigned with only a single entity.</entry>

            <entry>1.Login as customer user 2.Navigate to Administration
            &gt;Report designer &gt; Create 2. Do not select any entity during
            creation of report. 3.User creating this report is assigned with
            only one entity. 4. Save the report and run it. 5.User sees all
            the transactions related to multiple entities in the report which
            is not expected behavior as user is assigned to only one
            entity.</entry>

            <entry>Impacts Report Designer</entry>

            <entry>Report execution for user will be consistent with respect
            to the number of entities he is assigned to.</entry>

            <entry>Trade</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry>02279630</entry>

            <entry>MPS-63737</entry>

            <entry>Calendar alerts for Export Collection causes an SQL
            error</entry>

            <entry>1. Setup a customer with an Export Collection alert in
            alerts maintenance, any type of alert can be chosen 2. Observe
            whether an SQL error is recorded in the logs.</entry>

            <entry>Impacts Calendar Alerts</entry>

            <entry>Removed the applicant_ abbv_name from the query</entry>

            <entry>Trade <productname>Export Collection</productname></entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry>02278417</entry>

            <entry>MPS-65192</entry>

            <entry>Error received in report execution when migrated from FCC
            version 4.1 to FCC version 5.5</entry>

            <entry>
              <para>1. Use migrated DB from 4.1 to 5.5 2. Login as Customer
              user 3. Execute version 4.1 report.</para>
            </entry>

            <entry>Impacts Report Designer migration</entry>

            <entry>FCC will now handle the width in em. Once report is edited,
            the same width will be stored as percent.By default the width in
            v5.5 will be in percent</entry>

            <entry>System Features</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry>02279831</entry>

            <entry>MPS-63703</entry>

            <entry>LC amendment print does not open the PDF document</entry>

            <entry>1. Login as customer user 2. Navigate to Import Letter of
            Credit &gt; LC amendment &gt; From Existing LC 3. Open one
            transaction - click Save and open the print option to export 4.
            Download and open the PDF, it gives error - Failed to load PDF
            document</entry>

            <entry>Impacts LC Amendment PDF download</entry>

            <entry>For Narrative section, check is not handled properly, so
            handled the proper check</entry>

            <entry>Trade <productname>Import Letter of
            Credit</productname></entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry>02277684</entry>

            <entry>MPS-63619</entry>

            <entry>Unable to open exported PDF for SI Amendments</entry>

            <entry>1. Login as Customer user 2. Create an issue event for
            StandBy LC 2. Create an amendment event for the same with
            Narrative details 3. Submit the SI Amendment and open - Review and
            Print Details 4. Export the PDF from the popup 5. Open the PDF, an
            error is displayed - Failed to open PDF</entry>

            <entry>Impacts SI Amendments PDF download</entry>

            <entry>Updated the code for handling Narrative details</entry>

            <entry>Trade <productname>Issued StandBy LC</productname></entry>
          </row>
        </tbody>
      </tgroup>
    </informaltable>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Outstanding Issues</title>

    <para>This section lists the outstanding issues in this
    release.<informaltable>
        <tgroup cols="3">
          <colspec align="center" colwidth="180*"/>

          <colspec colwidth="589*"/>

          <colspec colwidth="231*"/>

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry align="center">Jira Id</entry>

              <entry align="center">Description</entry>

              <entry align="center">Product</entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry/>

              <entry>No action is happening on clicking of OK button at
              repricing add new loan screen for particular scenario</entry>

              <entry>Loan</entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry>MPS-63724</entry>

              <entry>Proper error should be shown for edit transaction for
              loan amount field</entry>

              <entry>Loan</entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable></para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Browser to Operating System Compatibility Matrix</title>

    <para>The matrix lists browser compatibility with various Operating
    Systems(OS).</para>

    <para>T - Tested</para>

    <para>S - Supported</para>

    <informaltable role="TEXT">
      <tgroup cols="10">
        <colspec colname="c2" colwidth="81*"/>

        <colspec colname="c3" colwidth="101*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="84*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="88*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="98*"/>

        <colspec colname="c9" colwidth="136*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="125*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="116*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="110*"/>

        <colspec colwidth="61*"/>

        <thead>
          <row>
            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Browser Name</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Applicable Version</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">Windows 7</entry>

            <entry valign="top">Windows 8.1</entry>

            <entry valign="top">Windows 10</entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>macOS 10.12 (Sierra)</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">macOS 10.13 (High Sierra)</entry>

            <entry valign="top">macOS 10.14 (Mojave)</entry>

            <entry valign="top">OSX EL Captain</entry>

            <entry valign="top">iOS (iPad)</entry>
          </row>
        </thead>

        <tbody>
          <row>
            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Chrome</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>86</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">T</entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>S</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Firefox</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>82</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">T</entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>S</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Microsoft Edge</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>44</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para/>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Internet Explorer</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>9</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para/>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Internet Explorer</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>10</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para/>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Internet Explorer</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>11</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">T</entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para/>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Safari</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>13</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>S</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top">
              <para>Safari</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>12.1</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top">
              <para>S</para>
            </entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>

            <entry valign="top"/>

            <entry valign="top">S</entry>
          </row>
        </tbody>
      </tgroup>
    </informaltable>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Deployment</title>

    <para>This patch deployment is an incremental upgrade from release
    <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_portal_previous_version1"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> to release <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_portal_version1"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>.</para>

    <warning>
      <para>Before upgrading, backup your database and current application
      data folders.</para>
    </warning>

    <para>Following is the deployment procedure to upgrade from release
    <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_portal_previous_version1"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> to release <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_portal_version1"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>:</para>

    <note>
      <para>
        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>For a new database installation and setup of application
            (deployment and redeployment of EAR), refer to the Installation
            Guide.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>This is a FCC Portal CORE release and does not include
            customer specific customizations. This CORE release needs to be
            merged with customer specific customizations, as required.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>Customers receiving customized release should refer to
            deployment section of corresponding release notes for any customer
            specific changes</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>It is advised to run the scripts from the Database specific
            SQL tools for example, SQL Developer for Oracle, IBM DataStudio
            for DB2. For DB2 it is advised to set the appropriate
            language/code page so that there will not be any
            truncation.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>The open API related script updates are added in each of the
            below listed database scripts.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </para>
    </note>

    <note>
      <para>
        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>The below migration scripts needs to be applied for the
            below tables manually only for those databases which have been
            created (Initialized) post FCC 6.0 release (i.e., 6.0, 6.0.0.1,
            6.0.0.2). Databases migrated from 5.x to the latest version need
            not execute the same.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>For Oracle: <programlisting>	
						ALTER table GTP_PERMISSION drop column OBJECTDATA;
						ALTER table GTP_ROLE drop column OBJECTDATA;
						ALTER table GTP_GROUP drop column OBJECTDATA; 

						ALTER TABLE GTP_ROLE ADD  OBJECTDATA LONG RAW null; 
						ALTER TABLE GTP_PERMISION ADD  OBJECTDATA LONG RAW null;
						ALTER TABLE GTP_GROUP ADD  OBJECTDATA LONG RAW null; 
					</programlisting></para>

            <para>For DB2: <programlisting>				
							ALTER table GTP_PERMISSION drop column OBJECTDATA;
							ALTER table GTP_ROLE drop column OBJECTDATA;
							ALTER table GTP_GROUP drop column OBJECTDATA ; 
 
							ALTER TABLE GTP_ROLE ADD OBJECTDATA VARCHAR(2000) for bit data;
							ALTER TABLE GTP_PERMISION ADD OBJECTDATA VARCHAR(2000) for bit data;
							ALTER TABLE GTP_GROUP ADD  OBJECTDATA VARCHAR(2000) for bit data;
					</programlisting></para>

            <para>For MYSQL: <programlisting>			
							ALTER table GTP_PERMISSION drop column OBJECTDATA;
							ALTER table GTP_ROLE drop column OBJECTDATA;
							ALTER table GTP_GROUP drop column OBJECTDATA; 
 
							ALTER TABLE GTP_PERMISSION MODIFY OBJECTDATA longblob;
							ALTER TABLE GTP_GROUP MODIFY OBJECTDATA longblob;
							ALTER TABLE GTP_ROLE MODIFY OBJECTDATA longblob;
					</programlisting></para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </para>
    </note>

    <para>For DB2:<itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para>
            <filename>MP_V<xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
            xpointer="ent_portal_version1"
            xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>_dml_db2.sql</filename>
          </para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist></para>

    <para>For MSSQL (Including MSSQL 2016 and above):<note>
        <para>All the customers using MSSQL must upgrade to MSSQL2016 or
        above, if using any older versions of MSSQL. Before upgrading, convert
        the sequences maintained in gtp_id_table. A sample utility script is
        shared for migrating to sequences in the SQL file,
        MP_V5.5.6.1_ddl_mssql.sql. Run this script only when no sequences are
        being used in the MSSQL.</para>
      </note><itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para>
            <filename>MP_V<xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
            xpointer="ent_portal_version1"
            xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>_dml_mssql.sql</filename>
          </para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist></para>

    <para>For MySQL:<itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para>
            <filename>MP_V<xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
            xpointer="ent_portal_version1"
            xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>_dml_mysql.sql</filename>
          </para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist></para>

    <para>For ORACLE:<itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para>
            <filename>MP_V<xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
            xpointer="ent_portal_version1"
            xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>_dml_oracle.sql</filename>
          </para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist></para>

    <important>
      <para>The following is the deployment procedure for Loan IQ
      scripts:</para>

      <para>For Loan IQ, the Scripts are packaged as a part of Fusion
      Corporate Channels delivery under FBCC_LoanIQ_Scripts.zip. Extract the
      zip and find the files under folders scripts\inquiry and scripts\events
      and place the combined scripts under Loan IQ’s installation respective
      folders of Server and Client (client is optional).</para>

      <para>For Loan IQ 7.5, refer to the scripts under 7.5 directory in the
      same location mentioned above.</para>

      <para>This release is verified against the following version of Loan IQ:
      <varname>7.5.1.4-HF2</varname></para>

      <para>There is a new trigger (Event trigger for loan inactivation by
      batch) to be set in Loan IQ, the details of trigger are provided in the
      <filename>FCC_integration_loan_IQ_en.pdf</filename>.</para>

      <para>For detailed deployment instructions, please follow Loan IQ
      Integration Guide FCC_integration_loan_IQ_en.pdf</para>
    </important>

    <important>
      <para>The following are the relevant versions of Opics and SFX</para>

      <para>
        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>This release is verified against the following version of
            Opics: 4.6.2.0 and 4.2.9.0.<note>
                <para>Opics integration is updated with password encryption,
                for detailed information refer
                <filename>FCC_integration_opics_en</filename> guide.</para>
              </note></para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </para>

      <para>SFX <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>Version: 3.1.3</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>Build : ad2ecb685fe</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist></para>
    </important>

    <note>
      <para>This release requires jdk1.8 and above for installation</para>
    </note>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Property and Configuration File Updates</title>

    <para>This section lists the updates made in Property files and
    Configuration files.</para>

    <para>The below properties are added in loan.properties file
    <programlisting>
# For the availability of Remittance Instruction section in Repricing screen below property key should be configured to 'true'.
# LoanIQ7.1 and earlier versions will not support Remittance Instruction. 
# Default value is [true]; Allowed values are [true/false/mandatory]. 
# Find the behavior of property when set with different values.
# mandatory : Remittance instructions are displayed in Initiate Repricing Screen. Selection of remittance instruction is mandatory.
# true : Remittance instruction grid is displayed in Initiate Repricing Screen. Selection of remittance instruction is not mandatory.
# false : Remittance instruction grid is not displayed in Initiate Repricing Screen and selection of remittance instruction is not possible.
remittance.instruction.section.required.for.repricing = true

#Property to show only borrower currencies instead of all facility currencies
 show.only.associated.borrower.currency = false
#Property to decide whether main facility currency needs to hide or not
 hide.main.facility.currency = false</programlisting></para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Interface File Updates</title>

    <para>This section lists the updates made in Interface files.</para>

    <para>This section has no updates in this release.</para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Localization Updates</title>

    <para>The following section describes about the localization changes made
    for the current release.</para>

    <para>The below entry is modified in core_en.properties file
    <programlisting>XSL_REPORT_DISPCOLDETAILS_WIDTH = Width (%):</programlisting></para>

    <para>The below entries are added/modified in common.js file
    <programlisting>ErrorForMandatoryRemittance : Please choose a Remittance instruction for disbursement of funds.
currencyValidationError: Unable to proceed as the currency has not been configured. Kindly reachout to your Relationship Manager.</programlisting></para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Build Package Updates</title>

    <para>This section lists the build package and library changes
    made.</para>

    <para>This section has no updates in this release.</para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Parameter Updates</title>

    <para>This section lists the updates made in parameters.xml.</para>

    <para>Parameter Id: "P780"</para>

    <para>Key: ALLOWED_PAYMENT_METHODS</para>

    <para>Usage: List of Payment Methods methods used for filtering out
    remittance instructions in Drawdown, Repricing and Increase
    Screens.</para>

    <para>Table Name: GTP_LARGE_PARAM_KEY AND GTP_LARGE_PARAM_DATA</para>

    <para>Below are required key and data columns for configuring this
    parameter.<programlisting>KEY_1 - bank_abbv_name, DATA_1 - Allowed Payment Method</programlisting></para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Reference Documents</title>

    <para>This section provides details for reference documents for
    configuration of property files, interfaces files, localisation files,
    parameters and customisation using the SDK. You can find these documents
    in the <filename>/Docs</filename> folder of your deliverable.</para>

    <orderedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>Property file information - FCC_tech_admin_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Interfaces file information - FCC_tech_admin_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Localisation file information - FCC_tech_admin_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Parameters information - FCC_tech_admin_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>SDK Documentation - FCC_installation_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Integration of Cash with MHUB -
        FCC_integration_cash_services_MHUB_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Integration with Loan IQ - FCC_integration_loan_IQ_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Integration with Opics - FCC_integration_opics_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Integration with TI -
        FCC_integration_trade_innovation_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Interfaces Migration - FCC Interfaces Migration Guide.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Integration with Fusion SeamlessFX -
        FCC_integration_SeamlessFX_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Integration with FCM - FCC_integration_FCM_en.pdf</para>
      </listitem>
    </orderedlist>
  </section>

  <para id="TOTALPAGE"/>
</article>
