<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<section condition="TITLE=Account Summary;ACCESS=AS_LP_UX" role="TOPIC">
  <title>Account Summary</title>

  <para role="TEXT">The <emphasis role="bold">Account Summary</emphasis>
  function allows you to see summary of various account types like current
  account, savings account and more. The Account Summary listing page is
  partitioned into following tabs: <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>All Account: Displays the account summary of account types like
        Term Deposit Account, Current Account, Savings Account, Loan Account
        and External Account.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Most Active Accounts: Displays the list of most active accounts
        the you have access to.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Group Accounts: Displays the accounts that are clubbed together
        to form a group. You can create a new group, edit an existing group
        and/or delete a group. You can filter the group accounts based on
        currency. Group Accounts only for the selected currency are
        displayed.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Payments and Collections: Displays the debit and credit history
        of the listed accounts.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist><note>
      <para>To look up for a particular account information you can either
      navigate to a related tab and the parser scrolls to the relevant section
      or you can scroll manually to the account information and the focus on
      the tab automatically gets adjusted.</para>
    </note></para>

  <para>The following image illustrates the Account Summary landing
  page:</para>

  <para><inlinemediaobject>
      <imageobject>
        <imagedata fileref="images/acc_sum_landing.png" width="165mm"/>
      </imageobject>
    </inlinemediaobject></para>

  <para>The <guiicon>Advance Filter</guiicon> presents you with various filter
  options like <emphasis role="bold">Entity</emphasis>, <emphasis
  role="bold">Account Number</emphasis>, <emphasis
  role="bold">Nickname</emphasis>, <emphasis role="bold">Currency</emphasis>
  and <emphasis role="bold">Equivalent Currency</emphasis>. Enter the relevant
  search criterion and apply the filter to list all the relevant account
  records.</para>

  <para>You can perform the following actions on the listed loan
  records:<itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Search</emphasis>: Enter any of the
        <guiicon>Advance Filter</guiicon> search criterion in the search box
        to display the required list of loan transactions.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">CSV Download</emphasis>: Download the list
        of loan transactions displayed on the dashboard.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><emphasis role="bold">Customize</emphasis>: You can customize
        the order in which the account information is displayed. You can
        achieve following customizations through this feature:<itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para>Select the columns that you wish to display, unselect the
              column names to hide the columns.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para>Click on lock icon to freeze the position of the column.
              The freezed columns are placed on the left of screen. You can
              freeze a maximum of three columns.</para>
            </listitem>

            <listitem>
              <para>You can drag and drop a column name to rearrange the table
              columns. Hover over multiple dots icon against each column name
              to, a hand icon appears, which suggests that the column is ready
              to be dragged and dropped.</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist><note>
            <para>This feature is available for all the tables of <xi:include
            href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
            xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>.</para>
          </note></para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist></para>
</section>
