<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<book lang="en">
  <bookinfo id="fcc_copyright">
    <legalnotice>
      <title>Copyright</title>

      <para role="TEXT">© <?dbtimestamp format="Y"?> Finastra International
      Limited, or a member of the Finastra group of companies (“Finastra”).
      All Rights Reserved. Confidential - Limited Distribution to Authorized
      Persons Only, pursuant to the terms of the license agreement by which
      you were granted a license from Finastra for the applicable software or
      services and this documentation. Republication or redistribution, in
      whole or in part, of the content of this documentation or any other
      materials made available by Finastra is prohibited without the prior
      written consent of Finastra. The software and documentation are
      protected as published or unpublished works and constitute a trade
      secret of Finastra International Limited, or a member of the Finastra
      group of companies, Head Office: 4 Kingdom Street, Paddington, London W2
      6BD, United Kingdom.</para>
    </legalnotice>

    <legalnotice>
      <title>Trademarks</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Finastra trademarks used in document and their
      respective sub-brands, and the logos used with some of these marks, are
      trademarks or registered trademarks of Finastra International Limited,
      or a member of the Finastra group of companies (“Finastra”) in various
      countries around the world. All other brand and product names are
      trademarks, registered trademarks, or service marks of their respective
      owners, companies, or organizations, may be registered, and should be
      treated appropriately.</para>
    </legalnotice>

    <legalnotice>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Finastra does not guarantee that any information
      contained herein is and will remain accurate or that use of the
      information will ensure correct and faultless operation of the relevant
      software, services or equipment. This document contains information
      proprietary to Finastra. Finastra does not undertake mathematical
      research but only applies mathematical models recognized within the
      financial industry. Finastra does not guarantee the intrinsic
      theoretical validity of the calculation models used.</para>

      <para>THE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THIS DOCUMENT AND THE GENERAL
      GUIDANCE OF FINASTRA STAFF DOES NOT TAKE THE PLACE OF QUALIFIED
      COMPLIANCE PERSONNEL OR LEGAL COUNSEL WITHIN YOUR INSTITUTION. FINASTRA
      CANNOT RENDER LEGAL, ACCOUNTING OR OTHER PROFESSIONAL SERVICES TO YOUR
      INSTITUTION. THE INFORMATION CONTAINED HEREIN IS GENERAL IN NATURE AND
      DOES NOT CONSTITUTE LEGAL ADVICE OR A LEGAL OPINION. CONSULT YOUR LEGAL
      COUNSEL FOR LEGAL ADVICE SPECIFIC TO YOUR SITUATION OR CIRCUMSTANCES OR
      TO ANSWER ANY LEGAL QUESTIONS. YOUR FINANCIAL INSTITUTION IS SOLELY
      RESPONSIBLE FOR CONFIGURING AND USING THE SOFTWARE OR SERVICES IN A WAY
      THAT MEETS POLICIES, PRACTICES, AND LAWS APPLICABLE TO YOUR INSTITUTION,
      INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION: (1) OPTIONS AND SELECTIONS MADE ON
      PROMPTS; (2) ENTRIES IN THE SOFTWARE PROGRAM; (3) PROGRAM SETUP; AND (4)
      DOCUMENTS PRODUCED BY THE SOFTWARE OR SERVICES. IT IS THE OBLIGATION OF
      THE CUSTOMER TO ENSURE THAT RESPONSIBLE DECISIONS ARE TAKEN WHEN USING
      FINASTRA PRODUCTS. INFORMATION IN THIS DOCUMENT IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE
      WITHOUT NOTICE AND DOES NOT REPRESENT A COMMITMENT ON THE PART OF
      FINASTRA.</para>
    </legalnotice>

    <legalnotice>
      <title>Feedback</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Do you have comments about our guides and online help?
      Please address any comments and questions to your local Finastra
      representative.</para>

      <para>Need more information? Read more about our products at <ulink
      url="http://www.finastra.com">http://www.finastra.com</ulink> or contact
      your local Finastra office at <ulink
      url="http://www.finastra.com/contact">http://www.finastra.com/contact</ulink>.</para>
    </legalnotice>

    <legalnotice>
      <para role="TEXT">Release month and year: <?dbtimestamp format="B Y"?></para>
    </legalnotice>
  </bookinfo>

  <colophon>
    <para id="TOTALPAGE"/>
  </colophon>
</book>
