<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>Admin and Default Roles</title>

  <para>Some default roles are set up in the system when it is initially
  installed. They should match most of a bank's needs, and serve as sample
  roles.</para>

  <section>
    <title>Admin Roles</title>

    <para>Three default roles are supplied and are automatically granted to
    administrators, as follows. These roles should never be deleted.</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para><literal moreinfo="none">sy_admin_user</literal> is granted to
        the customer administrator when a customer is created.</para>

        <para>In the default set-up, this role is initially granted only the
        right to set for himself any of the roles given by the bank
        administrator who created the company. As a first step, and before
        being able for instance to create his colleagues, this user would
        typically need to grant his own profile the right to create
        users.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><literal moreinfo="none">sy_bank_admin_user</literal> is granted
        to the bank administrator when a bank is created.</para>

        <para>The same as above apply for this user in the sense that it can
        initially only manipulate his own permissions. In a classical set-up
        this user would then receive all required permissions to create users
        for the bank middle office, even also customers, and to grant them
        permissions.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para><literal moreinfo="none">sy_bank_group_admin_user</literal> is
        granted to the bank group administrator when <xi:include
        href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
        xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> is installed.</para>

        <para>The same as above applies for his initial minimal permission. On
        top of the common bank administration permissions, he will typically
        grant himself the permission to create subsidiary banks. Note that
        this very specific role should not be granted to any other
        user.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Default Roles</title>

    <para>Refer to the Roles topic in the Technical Administration Guide for
    default role definitions.</para>
  </section>


</chapter>
