<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter condition="TITLE=Getting started" role="SECTION">
  <title>Getting Started</title>

  <para role="TEXT">This chapter introduces the Web interface through which
  you use <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />.</para>

  <section role="SECTION">
    <title>Welcome and Log In</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When you connect to <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> , you see the Welcome page.
    It has a list of the features in <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_applisump" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
    down the left-hand side, and items of recent news in the middle of the
    page.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Click <guibutton>Login to my account</guibutton> on the
    toolbar to log in. Enter your user ID, password and company name, then
    click <guibutton>Submit</guibutton>.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Your home page appears. This has a similar overall
    appearance to the Welcome page, but down the left-hand side is the main
    menu, and down the right-hand side is a portlet - an application runnning
    within the page - which is the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_Trade_C" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
    module. This provides a calendar and lists of recent events.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_applisump" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
    toolbar is the same on every page. There may be another toolbar above it,
    specific to your site; this is not covered in this documentation. At the
    left-hand end of the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_applisump" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
    toolbar is a link to your <guibutton>Home page</guibutton>. At the
    right-hand end are three icons: <inlinemediaobject>
        <imageobject>
          <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_logout.gif" />
        </imageobject>
      </inlinemediaobject>to log out, <inlinemediaobject>
        <imageobject>
          <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_systemfeatures.gif" />
        </imageobject>
      </inlinemediaobject>to access the System Features menu, and
    <inlinemediaobject>
        <imageobject>
          <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_toolbarhelp.gif" />
        </imageobject>
      </inlinemediaobject>to display the online help.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The only function you are likely to want to use on the
    System Features menu is <guibutton>Change Profile</guibutton>, which you
    use to change your language and your password. All the modules for
    handling trades are available from your main menu.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="SECTION">
    <title>Lists</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Many functions display a page that lists relevant
    transactions. These list pages have many things in common:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
           You can enter search criteria in a group of fields at the top of the page and click Search, to make the list show only records that match these criteria. These fields represent the most important fields in the transaction record, as do the columns in the table. 
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
           You can use wildcards in these fields. The wildcard character is an asterisk (*). You can use it anywhere in a field. 
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">On pages where the list might be very long - for example, if
          there are many transactions - the list is not displayed until you
          have entered the search criteria and clicked <emphasis
          role="bold">Search</emphasis>. Enter an asterisk in any of the
          search fields to get the entire list.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
           If your company has entities defined in its profile, then a 

          <guilabel />

           column and a search criterion field for 

          <emphasis role="bold">Entity</emphasis>

           appear in addition to the columns and fields mentioned in the individual chapters. 
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">You can click the heading of a column to make a triangular
          icon appear, which you can then click to sort the list on that
          column, in ascending or descending order.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">In most lists you can click in a row to process the
          transaction shown in that row. Depending on the list, you can edit,
          view, or delete the transaction, or create an amendment request for
          it. In some lists you click anywhere in the row; in some lists you
          click the <guibutton>System ID</guibutton> column; while some lists
          have icons you can click to edit, view or delete a transaction.
          Details are given in the sections for the individual
          functions.</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
  </section>

  <section role="SECTION">
    <title>Forms</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Most functions display an input form, either immediately
    you click the function or after you click a row in a list displayed by the
    function. These forms have many things in common:</para>

    <itemizedlist role="TEXT">
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Near the top right of a form, you'll see a free-floating menu on
        a coloured background, with the entries <guimenuitem>Show Form
        Summary</guimenuitem> and <guimenuitem>Top</guimenuitem>. This menu
        stays put as you scroll up and down the form. Clicking
        <guibutton>Top</guibutton> takes you back to the top of the form.
        Clicking <guimenuitem>Show Form Summary</guimenuitem> displays a menu
        of all the section headings in the form; you can click one to go
        straight to that section.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">If a field has a <inlinemediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_glass.gif" />
            </imageobject>
          </inlinemediaobject> (magnifying glass) icon by it, you can click
        the icon to see a popup list of values. Click a value to insert it in
        the field. This is most often used for currency fields.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">If a field has a <inlinemediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_search.gif" />
            </imageobject>
          </inlinemediaobject> icon by it, you can click the icon to see a
        popup list of predefined phrases. Click a phrase to insert it in the
        field. You can then edit the field further. This is most often used
        for free-format fields such as <guilabel>Other Information</guilabel>
        fields.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">In most date fields, you can enter the date in two ways:</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Select the first option button to enter the required date.
            Click the field and select the date from the calendar.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Select the second option button to enter a length of time.
            Insert the number of days/weeks/months/years in the first field.
            Select from the dropdown list: <literal>Days</literal>,
            <literal>Weeks</literal>, <literal>Months</literal> or
            <literal>Years</literal>.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">If a heading has a <inlinemediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_chevronright.gif" />
            </imageobject>
          </inlinemediaobject> icon by it, you can click the icon to expand
        the form, displaying a subsection that otherwise is not displayed.
        Click the <inlinemediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_chevrondown.gif" />
            </imageobject>
          </inlinemediaobject> icon to close the subsection again.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">This documentation describes each input form in detail,
    with a table describing each control (field, button, etc).</para>
  </section>

  <section role="SECTION">
    <title>Date and Amount Formats</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When entering a date in a date field, you can enter it
    in the form <replaceable>DD/MM/YYYY</replaceable> or
    <replaceable>DDMMYY</replaceable> if your locale is for instance France,
    or in the form <replaceable>MM/DD/YYYY</replaceable> or
    <replaceable>MMDDYY</replaceable> if your locale is for instance the
    USA..</para>

    <para role="TEXT"><informalexample>
        <para role="TEXT">For example, entering <literal moreinfo="none">180401</literal>
        produces a display of <literal moreinfo="none">18/04/2001</literal>,
        which in a French locale corresponds to 18th April 2001.</para>
      </informalexample></para>

    <para role="TEXT">When you enter an amount, the system automatically
    formats the value entered according to the currency selected. You can
    either enter the amount using the decimal and group delimiters of your
    locale (for example, respectively [,] and [space] for France, or [.] and
    [,] for Singapore), or directly as a series of digits.</para>

    <para role="TEXT"><informalexample>
        <para role="TEXT">For example, <literal moreinfo="none">123456.00</literal> in a
        Singaporean locale produces a display of <literal
        moreinfo="none">123,456.00</literal> if the currency involved is
        associated with 2 decimal places.</para>
      </informalexample></para>
  </section>
</chapter>
