<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter condition="TITLE=Introduction" role="SECTION">
  <title>Introduction</title>

  <para role="TEXT">This document provides an in-depth description of
  <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> for users at a client site.
  <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> gives you online access via a
  Web interface to asset services available to your company through your bank.
  It provides functions to initiate asset trades such as swaps, swaptions,
  etc, and follow up with them.</para>

  <para role="TEXT"><xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
  xpointer="ent_applisump" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
  consists of a set of modules all providing the same set of functions, but
  for different types of trade. Several other modules provide more general
  facilities, such as the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
  xpointer="ent_Business_R" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
  module, which you can use to send general questions to the bank.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">This <emphasis>Introduction</emphasis> chapter explains
  the basic concepts and terminology. The chapter <emphasis>Getting
  Started</emphasis> introduces the Web interface through which you use
  <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />. The chapter
  <emphasis>Functions</emphasis> gives an overview of a typical module,
  followed by a detailed description of each function. There is then a chapter
  for each module, introducing the trade type that it handles and giving a
  detailed description of its input form.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">There is also one chapter for each of the general modules:
  <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_Trade_C"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />, <xi:include
  href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_Business_R"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />, and <xi:include
  href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_Change_P"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />.</para>

  <section role="SECTION">
    <title>Types of User</title>

    <para role="TEXT"><xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_applisump" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> is
    used by companies that are customers of banks. We refer to these companies
    as "customers" or "clients" - we use these two terms
    interchangeably.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">A member of the staff of a client is called a "user". A
    user with administrator privileges is called an "administrator".</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The user interface has a section called System Features,
    accessed by clicking <inlinemediaobject>
        <imageobject>
          <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_systemfeatures.gif"
                     role="ICON_SUBMIT" width="10mm" />
        </imageobject>
      </inlinemediaobject>on the toolbar, and containing functions for
    administering and configuring the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_applisump" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
    system. The rest of the interface contains end-user functions. Which
    functions are available to a given user depends on that user's
    privileges.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="SECTION">
    <title>Audience</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This manual is addressed to a user at a client, and
    describes the end-user functions in the client user interface.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="SECTION">
    <title>Overview</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This section introduces the basic terminology used
    throughout <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />.</para>

    <section role="SECTION">
      <title>Products and Transactions</title>

      <para role="TEXT">In Misys's Portal systems, the different services that
      a bank can provide are called "products". Therefore, in this <xi:include
      href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> documentation, we may
      sometimes refer to the different asset trade types as products.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The communications between bank and client about an
      individual instance of a product typically consist of a sequence of
      messages from the client to the bank. For example, the communications
      regarding a swap would consist of the client's initial request to
      initiate the swap, possibly followed later by a request for an update.
      In <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />, no messages go from the
      bank to the client.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">These individual messages are called "transactions" or
      "transaction events". The whole set of messages concerning one instance
      of a individual product is called a "file" (this represents a "file of
      documents" in the system).</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The initial request from the client is often called
      the "initiation" of the file.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="SECTION">
      <title>System ID</title>

      <para role="TEXT">When a new file is created - for example, a client
      user initiates a new Swap request - <xi:include
      href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> gives it a unique
      reference number called its System ID. This is used throughout the
      system to identify it.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="SECTION">
      <title>Permissions</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The modules and functions that you, as an individual
      user, have access to, depend on permissions granted you by your
      company's <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_applisump"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> administrator. These
      permissions in turn have been granted to your company by the
      bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Your permissions are often referred to as privileges,
      authority or authorisation. These four terms are used
      interchangeably.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">These should not be confused with authentication,
      which means your login ID and password.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="SECTION">
      <title>Workflow</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The typical workflow is as follows. As a client user,
      you send a request to the bank on behalf of your company, to initiate a
      trade.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">You can later send a further message to the bank,
      amending your request.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Each module has functions that display lists of these
      transactions, so you can monitor their progress.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">When you are creating a transaction, you can save it
      at any time , without sending it, so that you or another user can work
      on it later. Its status is called Draft. On some lists it is called
      Incomplete.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">When you try to send a transaction ("submit" it), you
      might find that you have insufficient authority to do so - usually
      because you don't have the authority to handle the amount of money
      involved. It is then automatically saved but not sent, so that another
      user with greater authority can send it. This status is called Unsigned.
      On some lists it is called Uncontrolled.</para>
    </section>
  </section>
</chapter>
