<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>Functions</title>

  <para role="TEXT">For each product, there is a module that enables you to initiate,
  amend, and monitor trades on behalf of your company.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">These modules all have similar sets of functions. The basic functions
  found in all these modules are described in this chapter.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">For basic features common to all modules, such as basic terminology
  and the behaviour of lists, see chapters <emphasis>Introduction</emphasis>
  and <emphasis>Getting Started</emphasis>.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Portlets</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The Recent Pending Transactions and Recent Notifications lists
    within the Trade Events portlet on your home page show recent events in
    all modules. These lists are provided by the <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_Calendar"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> module. See chapter
    <emphasis>Calendar Module</emphasis> for details.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Validation and Submission</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Two types of validation are done when you fill in an input
    form.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">First, each field is validated as you enter it. Errors that can be
    detected by local validation of the field are indicated by a popup message
    as soon as the cursor leaves the field.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">When you have completed a form and you click
    <guibutton>Submit</guibutton>, the form is checked to ensure that all
    mandatory fields are filled in. If not, you get an error message and the
    first uncompleted mandatory field is highlighted.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Main Menu</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The main menu of <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> is down
    the left-hand side of your home page. It consists of links to the menus
    for the individual modules.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The number of items on the main menu therefore depends on which
    modules you have permissions for.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Functions</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This section lists the basic functions that you will find in a
    typical module. You enter the menu for a module by clicking the
    appropriate link on the main menu on your home page. The functions in the
    module for a particular product type handle only that product type. Only
    products for your own company are shown - you never see products for other
    companies.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The rest of this chapter describes these basic functions. The names
    of these functions may differ slightly between modules, and some modules
    may have other functions besides these, or not have all of these. These
    differences are described in the chapters for the individual
    modules.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In many cases the name of the function or set of functions includes
    the name or abbreviation for the product handled by the module. For
    example, in the Letter of Credit (LC) module, the menu item shown here as
    <guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Initiation</guimenuitem> is <guimenuitem
    moreinfo="none">LC Initiation</guimenuitem>.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In this chapter, where it is necessary to include the product type
    we call it <replaceable>product-type</replaceable>. Thus, in the LC
    module, <replaceable>product-type</replaceable> is LC.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">These are the basic functions:</para>

    <variablelist>
      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Initiation</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Set of functions for creating a request to initiate a product,
          and submitting the request to the bank.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Amendment</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Set of functions for creating a request to amend a product,
          and submitting the request to the bank.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Message to
        Bank</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Set of functions for creating a free-format message regarding
          a product, and submitting the message to the bank. In some modules
          this is called <guimenuitem>Update</guimenuitem>.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Pending</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Function to display a list of your company's pending
          transactions; that is, those that are have Draft or Unsigned status
          or are awaiting a reply from the bank. You can open transactions to
          edit or submit them.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Inquiry</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Function to display a list of products initiated by your
          company, so you can view their details and optionally print a hard
          copy of these details.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Maintenance</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Set of functions to carry out maintenance tasks, including
          deleting outdated transactions.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>
    </variablelist>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Operations</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Most functions display a form, with buttons which you click after
    filling it in. These buttons are as follows. These buttons do not all
    appear on every form.</para>

    <informaltable role="TEXT">
      <tgroup cols="2">
        <colspec colname="c1" colwidth="1.0*" />

        <colspec colname="c3" colwidth="8.0*" />

        <thead>
          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Operation</para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Description</para></entry>
          </row>
        </thead>

        <tbody>
          <row>
            <entry valign="middle"><para role="TEXT"> <guiicon
            moreinfo="none">Save</guiicon> </para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Save the transaction as a draft, so that
            you or another user can continue to work on it later. No
            validation is done. It is not sent to the bank.</para><para role="TEXT">Not
            present on <guibutton>Retrieve Unsigned</guibutton> forms, as
            these cannot be edited. </para></entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="middle"><para role="TEXT"> <guiicon
            moreinfo="none">Submit</guiicon> </para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Send the transaction to the bank. The
            form is validated, as described in section <emphasis>Validation
            and Submission</emphasis>. </para><para role="TEXT">If you do not have
            sufficient permissions (for example, to handle the amount you have
            requested), you get an error message and the transaction is not
            sent. Its status becomes Unsigned.</para></entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="middle"><para role="TEXT"> <guiicon
            moreinfo="none">Template</guiicon> </para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Save the transaction as a template, so
            that you or another user can base new transactions on it. No
            validation is done. It is not sent to the
            bank.</para><para role="TEXT">Present in forms that initiate a new
            file.</para></entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="middle"><para role="TEXT"> <guiicon
            moreinfo="none">Preview</guiicon></para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Open a popup window with full details of
            the Unsigned transaction and a <guibutton>Print</guibutton> button
            to print it out.</para><para role="TEXT">Present on <guibutton>Retrieve
            Unsigned</guibutton> forms. </para></entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="middle"><para role="TEXT"> <guiicon
            moreinfo="none">Cancel</guiicon> </para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Quit the form without saving it, and
            return to the main menu of the module.</para></entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="middle"><para role="TEXT"> <guiicon
            moreinfo="none">Help</guiicon> </para></entry>

            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Open a popup window displaying the
            online help.</para></entry>
          </row>
        </tbody>
      </tgroup>
    </informaltable>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Initiation Functions</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The <guisubmenu>Initiation</guisubmenu> part of the menu contains
    functions for creating a product initiation and submitting it to the
    bank.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>From Scratch</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Create a product initiation from scratch and optionally send it to
      the bank. In some modules, you can alternatively save it as a template,
      from which such initiations can be created.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays an input form for describing the details of
      the product requested. You use this form to create your initiation and
      validate it, save it as a draft, submit it to the bank (if you have
      sufficient authority), or save it as a template.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The input form is different for each product. For detailed
      descriptions of these input forms, see the chapters for the individual
      products.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>From Template</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Create a product initiation from a template and optionally submit
      it to the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of initiation templates created by
      users in your company. You can modify a template by clicking its
      <guiicon moreinfo="none">Edit</guiicon> <inlinemediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_edit.gif" role="ICON_EDIT"
                       width="4mm" />
          </imageobject>
        </inlinemediaobject> icon, or delete it by clicking its <guibutton
      moreinfo="none">Delete</guibutton> <inlinemediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_trash.gif" role="ICON_TRASH"
                       width="4mm" />
          </imageobject>
        </inlinemediaobject> icon.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click in the <guilabel moreinfo="none">Reference</guilabel> column
      to display the same input form as for <guimenuitem>From
      Scratch</guimenuitem>, but initialised with the data from the template.
      You use this form to create your initiation and validate it, save it as
      a draft, submit it to the bank (if you have sufficient authority), or
      save it again as a template.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Copy From</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Create a product initiation from an existing product of the same
      type.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of your company's existing products
      - that is, those that have been approved by the bank in response to an
      initiation request from your company..</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click in the <guilabel moreinfo="none">System Id</guilabel> column
      to display the same input form as for <guimenuitem>From
      Scratch</guimenuitem>, but initialised with the data from the existing
      product. You use this form to create your initiation and validate it,
      save it as a draft, submit it to the bank (if you have sufficient
      authority), or save it as a template.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Retrieve Draft</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Continue working on a product initiation that you or another user
      have already started and saved.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of Draft or Unsigned product
      initiations created by users in your company.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click in the <guilabel moreinfo="none">System Id</guilabel> column
      to open the initiation for further editing, after which you can again
      validate it, save it as a draft, submit it to the bank (if you have
      sufficient authority), or save it as a template.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Retrieve Unsigned</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Submit to the bank a product initiation that you or another user
      have previously started but been unable to submit.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of Unsigned product initiations
      created by users in your company.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click in the <guilabel moreinfo="none">System Id</guilabel> column
      to display a read-only summary of the initiation, from where you can
      submit it to the bank (if you have sufficient authority). You cannot
      edit the initiation from this function.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">You can submit multiple initiations in a single operation directly
      from the list. Click the box at the beginning of a row to select the
      row, then click <guibutton>Submit</guibutton> at the end of the list to
      submit all the selected initiations. The system will check that you have
      authorisation for multiple submissions.</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Amendment Functions</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The <guisubmenu>Amendment</guisubmenu> part of the menu contains
    functions for creating an amendment to an existing product, and submitting
    the amendment to the bank.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>From Existing</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Create an update for an existing product, and optionally submit it
      to the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of your company's existing products
      - that is, those that have been approved by the bank in response to an
      initiation request from your company..</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click a row to open an input form.You use this form to create your
      update and save it as a draft or submit it to the bank (if you have
      sufficient authority).</para>

      <para role="TEXT">You cannot open a product from this list if its status is
      <literal>Cancelled</literal>.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The input form is different for each product. For detailed
      descriptions of these input forms, see the chapters for the individual
      products.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Retrieve Draft</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Continue working on an update that you or another user have
      already started and saved.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of Draft and Unsigned updates
      created by users in your company.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click a row to open the update for further editing, after which
      you can save it again, or submit it (if you have sufficient
      authority).</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Retrieve Unsigned</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Submit to the bank an update that you or another user have
      previously started but been unable to submit.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of Unsigned updates created by users
      in your company.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click a row to display a read-only summary of the update, from
      where you can submit it to the bank if you have sufficient authority.
      You cannot edit the update from this function.</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Message to Bank (or Update)</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The <guisubmenu>Message to Bank</guisubmenu> (called
    <guimenuitem>Update</guimenuitem> in some modules) part of the menu
    contains functions for creating an free-format message regarding an
    existing product, and submitting the message to the bank.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>From Existing</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Create a message regarding an existing product, and optionally
      submit it to the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of your company's existing products
      - that is, those that have been approved by the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click a row to open an input form.You use this form to create your
      message and save it as a draft or submit it to the bank (if you have
      sufficient authority).</para>

      <para role="TEXT">You cannot open a product from this list if its status is
      <literal>Cancelled</literal>.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>From Discrepant</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Create a message in response to a reporting message from the bank,
      and optionally submit it to the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of your company's products for which
      there is a message waiting from the bank, of type Discrepancy Response.
      For a message of this type the bank requires an answer from your
      company.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click a row to open an input form.You use this form to create your
      message and save it as a draft or submit it to the bank (if you have
      sufficient authority).</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Action Required</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Create a message in response to a reporting message from the bank,
      and optionally submit it to the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of your company's products for which
      there is a message waiting from the bank, of type Customer Instructions,
      Consent Response, or Amendment Response. For a message of any of these
      types the bank requires an answer from your company.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click a row to open an input form.You use this form to create your
      message and save it as a draft or submit it to the bank (if you have
      sufficient authority).</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Retrieve Draft</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Continue working on a message that you or another user have
      already started and saved.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of Draft and Unsigned messages
      created by users in your company.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click a row to open the message for further editing, after which
      you can save it again, or submit it (if you have sufficient
      authority).</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Retrieve Unsigned</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Submit to the bank a message that you or another user have
      previously started but been unable to submit.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of Unsigned messages created by
      users in your company.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click a row to display a read-only form showing the message, from
      where you can submit it to the bank if you have sufficient authority.
      You cannot edit the update from this function.</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Inquiry and Maintenance</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This section describes the inquiry and maintenance functions found
    in the <guisubmenu>Pending</guisubmenu>,<guisubmenu> Inquiry</guisubmenu>,
    and<guisubmenu> Maintenance</guisubmenu> parts of the menu.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">First we describe the <guibutton>Output Format</guibutton> field,
    common to several of these functions.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Output Format</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Some functions in this part of the menu have a feature to let you
      choose the destination and format of the lists they display.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Below the search criteria fields is an <guilabel
      moreinfo="none">Output Format</guilabel> field, where you select the
      destination and format from a dropdown list:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>Screen</type> (default) displays the list on the same
          web page, in the normal list format.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>CSV</type> downloads the report to your machine as
          Comma-Separated Values file.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>Spreadsheet</type> downloads the report to your machine
          as a <productname class="trade">Microsoft Excel</productname>
          compatible file.</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">You would typically use the <literal>CSV</literal> or
      <literal>SpreadSheet</literal> option to export the list as a report, so
      you can use it or customize it in your office productivity tools. When
      you click <guibutton>Search</guibutton>, the browser displays the File
      Download prompt, where you can choose to save the file or open it.
      Opening it launches <productname>Excel</productname> if it is available
      on your workstation.</para>
    </section>

    <section id="LN_pending_lcs" role="ITEM">
      <title>Pending</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Check the status of pending transactions, and
      optionally edit or submit them.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of your company's
      transactions that are pending - that is Draft, Unsigned, or awaiting a
      reply from the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The <emphasis role="bold">Type</emphasis> column in
      the list shows the type of transaction:</para>

      <itemizedlist role="TEXT">
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>New</type> (an initation)</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>Amend</type> (an amendment)</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>Message</type> (a free-format message)</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">The <emphasis role="bold">Status</emphasis> column
      shows the current state of the transaction:</para>

      <itemizedlist role="TEXT">
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>Incomplete</type> (Draft)</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>Uncontrolled</type> (Unsigned)</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><literal>Submitted</literal> (awaiting a reply from the
          bank)</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">Each transaction is shown with one or two of the
      following three action icons, depending on its status:</para>

      <informaltable role="TEXT">
        <tgroup cols="2">
          <colspec colname="c1" colwidth="2.0*" />

          <colspec colname="c2" colwidth="8.0*" />

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Symbol</para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Description</para></entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                  <imageobject>
                    <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_edit.gif"
                               role="ICON_EDIT" width="4mm" />
                  </imageobject>
                </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Open the transaction to edit it (same
              as selecting it in <guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Retrieve
              Draft</guimenuitem>). This button is present on transactions
              with Incomplete (Draft) or Uncontrolled (Unsigned)
              status.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                  <imageobject>
                    <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_lock.gif"
                               role="ICON_LOCK" width="4mm" />
                  </imageobject>
                </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Open the transaction in non-editable
              form to submit it to the bank (same as selecting it in
              <guisubmenu>Retrieve Unsigned</guisubmenu>). This button is
              present on transactions with Uncontrolled (Unsigned)
              status.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                  <imageobject>
                    <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_popup.gif"
                               role="ICON_POPUP" width="4.5mm" />
                  </imageobject>
                </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Open a popup window displaying the
              details of the product. This button is present on transactions
              that have been submitted to the bank.</para></entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable>
    </section>

    <section id="LN_inquiry" role="ITEM">
      <title>Inquiry</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Check the status, details and history of products.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of your company's existing products
      - that is, those that have been approved by the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The <emphasis role="bold">Status</emphasis> column
      shows the current state of the product and can have the following
      values:</para>

      <itemizedlist role="TEXT">
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>New</type> is the state of a product after its
          successful initiation,</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>Amended</type> is its state after an amendment has been
          applied,</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>Updated</type> is the generic state generally given by
          the bank as a follow-up to a free format message.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT"><type>Other</type> statuses are available on the bank side and
          can be used freely by its Trade Services team when generating a Bank
          towards Client transaction (see the <emphasis>User Manual -
          Bank</emphasis> for further details on the bank reporting features).
          Hence the state of a transaction record could be
          <type>Accepted</type>, <type>Settled</type>, <type>Cancelled</type>,
          <type>Extended</type> or <type>Purged</type>.</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">Each record is shown with two action icons:</para>

      <informaltable role="TEXT">
        <tgroup cols="2">
          <colspec colname="c1" colwidth="2.0*" />

          <colspec colname="c2" colwidth="8.0*" />

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Symbol</para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Description</para></entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                  <imageobject>
                    <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_popup.gif"
                               role="ICON_POPUP" width="4.5mm" />
                  </imageobject>
                </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Open a popup window displaying the
              current details of the product.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                  <imageobject>
                    <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_folder.gif"
                               role="ICON_FOLDER" width="4mm" />
                  </imageobject>
                </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">(History) Display the Product
              Dashboard, described in section <emphasis>Product
              Dashboard</emphasis>. </para></entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Maintenance</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The functions in this part of the menu carry out
      various maintenance tasks.</para>

      <note role="TEXT">
        <para role="TEXT">Deleted records are physically removed from the system.
        Deletions should therefore be done with great care!</para>
      </note>

      <section role="TEXT">
        <title>Set Entity</title>

        <para role="TEXT">Only present if your company has entities.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">Assign an entity to a product that currently has none.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of products that have no entity
        assigned. Click in the <guilabel>System Id</guilabel> column to open a
        form where you can assign an entity. All transactions of the selected
        product are updated.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">No particular permissions are needed for this action.</para>
      </section>

      <section role="ITEM">
        <title>Set Reference</title>

        <para role="TEXT">Assign a customer reference to a product that currently has
        none.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of products that have no reference
        assigned. Click in the <guilabel>System Id</guilabel> column to open a
        form where you can assign a reference. All transactions of the
        selected product are updated.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">No particular permissions are needed for this action.</para>
      </section>

      <section role="TEXT">
        <title>Unsigned</title>

        <para role="TEXT">Delete Draft or Unsigned transactions that are out of date and
        will never be submitted.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of Draft or Unsigned
        transactions.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">Click rows to select them (click anywhere in the row - a tick
        appears at the left-hand end), then click <guibutton>Delete selected
        transactions</guibutton> at the end of the list to delete them. The
        system will check that you have sufficient authorisation.</para>
      </section>

      <section role="TEXT">
        <title>Purged</title>

        <para role="TEXT">Delete purged transactions.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of transactions that have been
        marked as <type>Purged</type> by the bank.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">You cannot initiate further amendments or messages on such a
        transaction, and can only use it for inquiry purposes, or as a basis
        for a new transaction using the <guibutton>Copy from</guibutton>
        function, if the module has such a function.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">Click rows to select them (click anywhere in the row - a tick
        appears at the left-hand end), then click <guibutton>Delete selected
        transactions</guibutton> at the end of the list to delete them. The
        system will check that you have sufficient authorisation.</para>
      </section>

      <section role="TEXT">
        <title>Rejected</title>

        <para role="TEXT">Delete rejected transactions.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of transactions that have been
        rejected (marked as <type>Not Processed</type>) by the bank.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">You cannot initiate further amendments or messages on such a
        transaction, and can only use it for inquiry purposes, or as a basis
        for a new transaction using the <guibutton>Copy from</guibutton>
        function, if the module has such a function.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">Click rows to select them (click anywhere in the row - a tick
        appears at the left-hand end), then click <guibutton>Delete selected
        transactions</guibutton> at the end of the list to delete them. The
        system will check that you have sufficient authorisation.</para>
      </section>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Product Dashboard</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When you click <inlinemediaobject>
        <imageobject>
          <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_folder.gif" role="ICON_FOLDER"
                     width="4mm" />
        </imageobject>
      </inlinemediaobject> in a row in the list displayed by the
    <guimenuitem>Inquiry</guimenuitem> function, a page is displayeed giving
    full details of the product whose row you clicked. This page is called the
    Product Dashboard. It shows a number of portlets:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Consolidated Summary View</para>

        <para role="TEXT">Basic reference information about the product, for example its
        system ID.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Outstanding</para>

        <para role="TEXT">Graph showing amount outstanding</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Actions</para>

        <para role="TEXT">Menu of links to initiate appropriate actions or related new
        products directly from this page.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">History</para>

        <para role="TEXT">List of events on this product. Click <guibutton>Switch to
        thread history</guibutton> or <guibutton>Switch to standard
        history</guibutton> to switch between two views.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Pending Transactions</para>

        <para role="TEXT">List of transactions on this product that are pending. This is
        just like the list described for the
        <guimenuitem>Pending</guimenuitem> function (see section
        <emphasis>Pending</emphasis>), but has entries for the one product
        only.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Consolidated Charge View</para>

        <para role="TEXT">List of consolidated charges.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">List of Attachments</para>

        <para role="TEXT">List of items attached to transactions on the product. You can
        click on a row in the list to download an attachment.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>History Report</title>

      <para role="TEXT">In the History portlet within the Product Dashboard, you can click
      in the <emphasis role="bold">Release</emphasis> date column to open a
      popup window showing full details of each event. Within the popup, the
      <guilabel moreinfo="none">Event Details</guilabel> section shows the key
      details of the event. It shows any additional instructions and
      attachments added by users at your company, and the bank's comments and
      attachments given in reporting messages.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Here are some examples covering various types of
      transaction:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">For an initiation, a summary of details of the new product,
          such as the system and reference numbers, the amount and dates are
          shown. The system also displays the full set of data submitted by a
          user at your company to initiate the product.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">For an amendment, only the information related to the
          amendment itself is shown, such as the increase of amount, a new
          expiry date or tolerance.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">For a message from the bank to the client, only a reminder of
          the references and the type of transaction (<type>Reporting</type>)
          are displayed, together with the instructions and comment text
          fields.</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">If the <guilabel moreinfo="none">Event Details</guilabel> header
      in the popup window shows a <guilabel moreinfo="none">Release
      Date/Time</guilabel>, it means the time the validated transaction event
      was released by your company to the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The <guilabel moreinfo="none">Date/Time</guilabel>
      field that accompanies a <guilabel moreinfo="none">Bank
      Message</guilabel> header means the time the reporting message was
      released by the bank to the customer.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">You can also export the history report as an external
      file in <type>PDF</type> format, by clicking <emphasis
      role="bold"><literal><literal>Export</literal></literal></emphasis>.</para>
    </section>
  </section>
</chapter>
