<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>About This Manual</title>

  <para role="TEXT">This document describes the usage of Opics Portal R4.x and its modules
  for users at the client site. Opics Portal provides online access using web
  interface to asset services available to your organization through your
  bank.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">It facilitates performing various functions to initiate asset trades,
  such as Foreign Exchange, Loans, Fund Transfers, etc.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">Opics Portal comprises a set of modules performing a similar set of
  functions, but for different types of trade. Several other modules provide
  more general facilities, such as the Foreign Exchange module, which helps
  you to perform an FX trade.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">This chapter covers the basic concepts and terminology used throughout
  the portal. The next chapter <emphasis>Getting Started</emphasis> introduces
  the Opics Portal and helps you to access it using a web interface. The
  subsequent chapters provide information about specific modules and their
  respective functions.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">The document also helps you to understand the components of trade
  calendar used in tracking trade events and describes how to change the
  profiles of portal users.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Types of User</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Opics Portal is used by companies that are customers of banks. The
    terms "customers" and "clients" are used interchangeably in this
    document.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The portal is generally used by:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">User</para>

        <para role="TEXT">A member of the staff of a client who performs trade functions
        using the portal.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Administrator</para>

        <para role="TEXT">A user with administrative privileges who manages permissions
        and configurations of the portal.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">The functions available to a user depend on the permissions
    configured by the administrator.</para>

    <tip>
      <para role="TEXT">The <emphasis>System Features</emphasis> section contains various
      fields for administering and configuring the functions of the Opics
      Portal system. To access this section, click <inlinemediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata depth="17.25pt"
                       fileref="../images/icon_systemfeatures.GIF"
                       width="17.25pt" />
          </imageobject>
        </inlinemediaobject> on the toolbar.</para>
    </tip>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Intended Audience</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This document provides information to the end-users at client site
    and describes the functions available in the client user interface.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Overview</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This section introduces the basic terminology used throughout Opics
    Portal.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Products and Transactions</title>

      <para role="TEXT">In Misys's Portal systems, the different services that a bank can
      provide are called "products". Therefore, in Opics Portal documentation,
      we refer to the different asset trade types as products.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The communications between a client and the bank about an
      individual instance of a product typically consist of a sequence of
      messages from the client to the bank. For example, the communications
      regarding a forward FX trade consists of the client's initial request to
      initiate the trade, possibly followed by a request for an update
      later.</para>

      <para role="TEXT"><emphasis>Note</emphasis>: In Opics Portal, no messages are sent
      from the bank to the client.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">These individual messages are called "transactions" or
      "transaction events". The entire set of messages concerning one instance
      of an individual product is called a "file" (represented by a "file of
      documents" in the system).</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The initial request from the client is often called the
      "initiation" of the file.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>System ID</title>

      <para role="TEXT">When a new file is created – for example, a user initiates a new
      FX request – Opics Portal assigns it a unique reference number called
      the System ID. This number is used by the portal to identify it.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Workflow</title>

      <para role="TEXT">In a typical workflow, as a user representing your organization,
      you send a request to the bank to initiate a trade. Besides, you can
      send additional messages to the bank, amending your original
      request.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Each module provides functions that display the list of
      transactions that helps you to monitor their progress. When you create a
      transaction, you can save it without sending it to the bank, so that you
      or another user can review or amend it later. This status is called
      Draft or Incomplete.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Nevertheless, while submitting a transaction, if the message is
      saved but not sent, it indicates that you do not have the designated
      authority to handle the amount of money involved in the transaction. In
      such a case, another user, with permissions to perform higher value
      transactions, can submit it. This status is called Unsigned or
      Uncontrolled.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Permissions</title>

      <para role="TEXT">For a user, the access rights to individual modules and functions
      depend on the permissions configured by your organization’s portal
      administrator. These permissions in turn are granted to your
      organization by the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The permissions are often referred to as
      <emphasis>privileges</emphasis>, <emphasis>authority</emphasis>, or
      <emphasis>authori</emphasis><emphasis>zat</emphasis><emphasis>ion</emphasis>.
      These four terms are used interchangeably throughout the
      document.</para>

      <para role="TEXT"><emphasis>Caution</emphasis>: The terms
      <emphasis>permissions</emphasis>, <emphasis>privileges</emphasis>,
      <emphasis>authority</emphasis>, and <emphasis>authorization</emphasis>
      do not signify <emphasis>authentication</emphasis>, which means the
      login credentials to access the portal.</para>
    </section>
  </section>
</chapter>
