<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>Working with Reports</title>

  <info />

  <para role="TEXT">This chapter describes how to view reports and take appropriate
  actions for all modules using Opics Portal. It also helps you to perform
  inquiries, view pending transactions, and execute reports across all
  modules.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>About Reports</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Opics Portal facilitates you to browse through all the
    acknowledgements and notifications sent by the bank, or through
    consolidated lists of pending transactions or existing records.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In the portal <emphasis>Home page</emphasis>, click
    <emphasis>Reports</emphasis><emphasis />and select from the following
    group of functions. Some of these functions are similar to the Pending,
    Inquiry, and Maintenance functions as described in the chapter
    <emphasis>Portal Functions</emphasis>, but they show transactions across
    all products.</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT"><emphasis role="bold">Review Reporting</emphasis>: To review all
        transactional messages sent by the bank, whether acknowledgements to
        transaction events initiated by the client, new events reported by the
        bank's back-office on an existing record, or new notifications. The
        details of each transaction event can also be retrieved from the
        list.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT"><emphasis role="bold">Pending Transactions</emphasis>: As
        described in chapter
        <emphasis>Portal</emphasis><emphasis>Functions</emphasis>, but shows
        transactions for all products.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT"><emphasis role="bold">Action Required</emphasis> : To perform
        this function, appropriate user permissions are required.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT"><emphasis role="bold">Inquiry</emphasis>: As described in
        chapter <emphasis>Portal</emphasis><emphasis>Functions</emphasis>, but
        shows transactions for all products.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT"><emphasis role="bold">Report Execution</emphasis>: To execute a
        report designed by an authorized administrator.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">The subsequent sections provide detailed explanation about using
    these functions and working with reports.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Review Reporting</title>

    <para role="TEXT">You can view a list of all transactional messages sent by the bank,
    for all products in Opics Portal. In the portal <emphasis>Home
    page</emphasis>, click <emphasis>Reports </emphasis>and select
    <emphasis>Review Reporting</emphasis>.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Specify the following and click <emphasis>Search</emphasis> to view
    transaction details:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Specify the <emphasis>System ID</emphasis> and <emphasis>Bank
        Ref</emphasis> number.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Indicate the period for the report from the
        <emphasis>From</emphasis> and <emphasis>To</emphasis> fields.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Select the <emphasis>Product</emphasis> for which the report is
        retrieved and specify the <emphasis>Output Format</emphasis> for the
        report.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Click <emphasis>Search</emphasis> to display reports.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Output</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The result displays the following details for the report:</para>

      <informaltable frame="all">
        <tgroup cols="2">
          <colspec colname="column-1" colwidth="2668*" />

          <colspec colname="column-2" colwidth="6080*" />

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry>Field</entry>

              <entry>Description</entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">
                  <guilabel>System ID</guilabel>
                </para>
              </entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">Specifies a unique reference number generated by for the
                transaction.</para>
              </entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">
                  <guilabel>Bank Ref</guilabel>
                </para>
              </entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">Identifies the bank's internal reference number assigned
                by the bank's back office to the transaction.</para>
              </entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">
                  <guilabel>Type</guilabel>
                </para>
              </entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">Indicates the type of transaction.</para>

                <para role="TEXT">Valid transaction types are:</para>

                <itemizedlist>
                  <listitem>
                    <para role="TEXT"><guibutton>New</guibutton> (for an initiation of a
                    new transaction)</para>
                  </listitem>

                  <listitem>
                    <para role="TEXT"><guibutton>Amend</guibutton> (for an amendment an
                    existing transaction)</para>
                  </listitem>

                  <listitem>
                    <para role="TEXT"><guibutton>Message</guibutton> (for any of the free
                    format / update message available with all the
                    products)</para>
                  </listitem>

                  <listitem>
                    <para role="TEXT"><guibutton>Reporting</guibutton> (if the transaction
                    event is not initiated by the client and is, therefore, an
                    update message initiated and sent by the bank on a given
                    transaction record)</para>
                  </listitem>
                </itemizedlist>
              </entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">
                  <guilabel>Counterparty</guilabel>
                </para>
              </entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">Identifies the name of the beneficiary in the
                transaction.</para>
              </entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">
                  <guilabel>Ccy</guilabel>
                </para>
              </entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">Indicates a three-digit currency code of the transaction
                record.</para>
              </entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">
                  <guilabel>Amount</guilabel>
                </para>
              </entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">Indicates the transaction amount, that is, the amount
                involved in the current event.</para>

                <para role="TEXT">This column therefore contains:</para>

                <itemizedlist>
                  <listitem>
                    <para role="TEXT">The total amount of the transaction upon its
                    creation (i.e. when the transaction type is New)</para>
                  </listitem>

                  <listitem>
                    <para role="TEXT">Only the increase or decrease of amount for a
                    modified transaction</para>
                  </listitem>

                  <listitem>
                    <para role="TEXT">A blank value in all other cases, since no amount is
                    associated with other types of event</para>
                  </listitem>
                </itemizedlist>
              </entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">
                  <guilabel>Release</guilabel>
                </para>
              </entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1">
                <para role="TEXT">Is the date when the customer initially released the
                transaction event to the bank.</para>
              </entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable>

      <para role="TEXT">Click the action icon of a transaction event to display more
      information about the transaction. This opens a popup window with the
      following details:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">The top of the page contains the summary information of the
          event and is common across the various products. It is composed of a
          first section summarizing the event details (such as its dates, its
          references and amount).</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">A second optional section shows additional details, such as
          the application date and the issuing bank’s name, provided by the
          input user when preparing the transaction event. It is here that the
          free format text or an optional file attachment is shown if the
          transaction event was a free format / update message.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">And finally a third section shows the details of the actual
          reporting message as created by the bank and the updated product
          status for the transaction after this event, plus any comments or
          the bank's attachments. It displays information about the contract,
          such as the type of contract, expiration details, currency, amount,
          etc.</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">The <emphasis>Reporting Status</emphasis> in the popup shows
      whether the event has been successfully acknowledged by the bank and
      accordingly what is its updated state.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The possible values of the product status have already been
      explained in the chapters on the Inquiry functions for the various
      products. As a reminder, they are:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Rejected indicates that the related event has not been
          approved by the bank</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">New indicates the state of any product after its successful
          initiation</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Amended is only applicable if a transaction is successful
          amendment</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Updated is the generic state generally given by the bank as a
          follow-up to a free format message transaction</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Purged is set by the bank to notify its technical termination
          of a given record</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Other statuses can be freely used by the bank with eventually
          its own interpretations (Accepted, Settled, Cancelled and
          Extended)</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">The rest of the page beyond the horizontal separator shows the
      most recently updated detailed information on the transaction record as
      validated by the bank through its reporting. It is specific to each
      product.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">You can also print out the whole content of the popup window or
      export it to a PDF file for your reference.</para>

      <note>
        <para role="TEXT">: Refer to corresponding chapters on the individual product
        modules for further details on the names used to describe each
        field.</para>
      </note>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Pending Transactions</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The portal also displays the status of pending transactions as
    incomplete, where you can select a transaction and thereby submit it to
    the bank for its completion.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In the <emphasis>Reports</emphasis> menu, click <emphasis>Pending
    Transactions </emphasis>to view the status of transactions or to submit an
    incomplete transaction.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">For more information about pending transactions, refer to chapter
    <emphasis>Portal Functions</emphasis> of this document.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Actions Required</title>

    <para role="TEXT">You can perform required actions on the transactions if appropriate
    administrative privileges are configured for your account.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In the <emphasis>Reports</emphasis> menu, click <emphasis>Actions
    Required </emphasis>to view the list of transaction records for customer
    action.</para>

    <note>
      <para role="TEXT">: Contact the system administrator of your organization for these
      permissions.</para>
    </note>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Making an Inquiry</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Opics Portal helps you to perform inquiries for all types of
    transactions.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In the <emphasis>Reports</emphasis> menu, click
    <emphasis>Inquiry</emphasis><emphasis>, </emphasis>specify the required
    fields, and click <emphasis>Search</emphasis> to view details of a
    transaction for a particular module in the portal.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">For general information about inquiries, refer to chapter
    <emphasis>Portal Functions</emphasis> or for information performing
    inquiries on individual modules, refer to the corresponding section of
    this document.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Reports Execution</title>

    <para role="TEXT">You can execute reports in Opics portal. In the
    <emphasis>Reports</emphasis> menu, click <emphasis>Report Execution,
    </emphasis>specify the <emphasis>Report Name</emphasis>, and click
    <emphasis>Search</emphasis> to view the report.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">You can click the report name to display the selected report. The
    report may provide a criteria zone, so that you can enter search patterns.
    You can also select the output format: Screen, CSV export, SpreadSheet
    (Excel) export or PDF export.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Click <emphasis>Search</emphasis> to execute the report.</para>

    <note>
      <para role="TEXT">: For executing reports, appropriate permissions and authorization
      is required for your account.</para>
    </note>
  </section>
</chapter>
