<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter condition="TITLE=Trade Message Center;PERM=mc_access;ACCESS=MC"
         role="TOPIC">
  <title><xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_Trade_M_C"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> (Reports) Module</title>

  <para role="TEXT">The <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
  xpointer="ent_Trade_M_C" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> is
  the cross-product central module of <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
  xpointer="ent_applisump" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> enabling
  you, as a user at a client, to see consolidated lists of transactions from
  all modules.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Overview</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This module contains no functions for creating or
    amending transactions. It contains functions similar to those in other
    modules, for listing existing transactions and their details. Whereas each
    other module shows only transactions for the product that that module
    handles, this module shows transactions for all products.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Click <guibutton>Reports</guibutton> on the main menu on
    your home page to get to the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_Trade_M_C" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
    menu.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Functions</title>

    <para role="TEXT">All the functions in this module handle products of all types, that
    is, they show products from every module.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The functions in this module are:</para>

    <variablelist>
      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Pending
        Transactions</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Function to display a list of your company's pending
          transactions; that is, those that are have Draft or Unsigned status,
          and those that have been submitted to the bank but have not yet been
          acknowledged by them. From this list, you can open those that have
          Draft or Unsigned status to edit or submit them. This takes you to
          the appropriate pagein the module for the appropriate
          product.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Batch
        Submission</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">If you have appropriate permission in your profile, submit
          multiple records to the bank in a single operation. A check box
          appears by each record in the list, and a button at the end of the
          screen submits the selected records.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Inquiry</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Function to display a list of your company's files (that is,
          the set of transactions on one instance of a product) for all types
          of product, so you can view their details or history, and optionally
          print a hard copy of their details.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Report
        Execution</guimenuitem></term>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Execute a report, designed by an authorized
          administrator.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>
    </variablelist>
  </section>

  <section id="TMC_pending_transactions_function" role="ITEM">
    <title>Pending Transactions</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Check the status of pending transactions, and optionally
    edit or submit them.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">This function is the same as described in section
    <emphasis>Pending</emphasis> in chapter <emphasis>Functions</emphasis>,
    except that it shows transactions for all products.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Batch Submission</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Submit multiple records for multiple products.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of all unsigned transactions, for all
    products.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">If you have sufficient authorisation in your profile, you can submit
    multiple records in a single operation. Click rows to select them, then
    click the button at the end of the list to submit them.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Inquiry</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Check the status, details and history of products</para>

    <para role="TEXT">This function is the same as described in section
    <emphasis>Inquiry</emphasis> in chapter <emphasis>Functions</emphasis>,
    except that it shows products of all types.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Report Execution</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Execute a report designed by an authorized administrator.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of existing
    reports.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Click the link to display the selected report. The
    report may include search criteria fields, so that you can enter search
    patterns. You can also select the output format:
    <guilabel>Screen</guilabel>, <guilabel>CSV</guilabel> export,
    <guilabel>SpreadSheet</guilabel> (<productname>Excel</productname>) export
    or <guilabel>PDF</guilabel> export. Click <guibutton
    moreinfo="none">Search</guibutton> to execute the report.</para>
  </section>
</chapter>
