<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>Trade Calendar</title>

  <para role="TEXT">This chapter describes a set of screens that provides an innovative
  type of report whose results are presented in a calendar. This feature
  provides an online front-end to track the events related to user
  transactions.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">For example, it helps an exporter to track in advance the upcoming
  expiry date of a letter of credit issued in his or her favor, or a customer
  to anticipate the approaching maturity date of a loan.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Overview</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Using the <emphasis>Trade Calendar</emphasis> module you can track
    the events related to your transactions initiated through the Portal,
    together with any custom events (like appointments or reminders) related
    to the activity of your company, in much the same way that you would
    through a shared electronic calendar.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">This module enables you to monitor key dates related to the products
    handled by the system, as well as adding your own custom events or alerts,
    turning your Portal page into an automated and customized
    scheduler.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The calendar appears on your home page, together with today's
    events. It is also accessible as a full screen application where events
    can be displayed by day or month or by type over a longer period of time
    in the <emphasis>Milestone View</emphasis>. For any event related to an
    existing transaction, a dedicated link gives you access to the transaction
    details and history through a single click.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The following sections describe the three main components of the
    <emphasis>Trade Calendar</emphasis> viz. the Calendar Component, the Trade
    Events Component, and the Application Component.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Calendar Component</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This component displays the calendar itself. It displays a calendar
    for the month, the current business date in your time zone highlighted,
    and serves as a table of contents to access the details of any date. Click
    a day to see a full page view of that day's events. Click the month name
    to see a full-page view of the month's events. Click the arrows around the
    month name to see the previous and following months.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Days associated with key dates are automatically highlighted with a
    specific background color. With this visual information, it is easy to
    detect right from the home page the key transactional events taking place
    during the month.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">A sample view of the calendar is given below. In this figure, no
    event is associated with any date of the month):</para>

    <figure>
      <info />

      <mediaobject>
        <imageobject>
          <imagedata depth="141.75pt" fileref="calander.GIF" width="166.5pt" />
        </imageobject>
      </mediaobject>
    </figure>

    <para role="TEXT">Figure: Trade Calendar</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Trade Events Component</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This component summarizes the key events of the current date and
    displays various alerts related to pending transactions or recent
    notifications. This section of the screen is composed of three
    subsections, each covering a specific type of event. Depending on your
    site, you may not have all three of these subsections.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Trade Events</title>

      <para role="TEXT">This list is a summary of all the events of the current day.
      Events shown are those for your company's transactions, plus any custom
      events manually added by any of your company's users.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The transactions displayed are the records bearing a key date
      equal to the current business date.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Recent Pending Transactions</title>

      <para role="TEXT">This list shows the most recent pending transactions initiated
      within your company, for any product and any type of transaction,
      whether initiation, amendment or message. Pending means
      <emphasis>Incomplete</emphasis> (Draft) or
      <emphasis>Uncontrolled</emphasis> (Unsigned), and hence not yet sent to
      the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Each entry shows the transaction's <emphasis>System ID</emphasis>,
      followed by the product code and the transaction type
      (<emphasis>New</emphasis>, <emphasis>Amend</emphasis>, or
      <emphasis>Message</emphasis>). Click the <emphasis>System ID</emphasis>
      to open the transaction record in the appropriate mode for its status.
      That is, a transaction that only needs to be signed opens in
      non-editable mode, whereas an incomplete record opens in the edit form
      for its transaction type.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">To avoid over-crowding your home page, the list shows, by default,
      only the 5 most recent such transactions (sorted by input date). This
      can be changed by setting a different value in the relevant
      configuration file.</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Application Component</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When you click a date or the month name in the <emphasis>Trade
    Calendar</emphasis> component on your home page, it opens the calendar
    application to show a full-page view displaying the following.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Types of Calendar View</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The full-screen view has a calendar just like that on the home
      page, on the left-hand side. This is called <emphasis>Standard
      view</emphasis>. Click <emphasis>Switch to Milestones View</emphasis>
      beneath it is to switch to <emphasis>Milestone View</emphasis>.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">In <emphasis>Standard view</emphasis>, the calendar is limited to
      one month and you can enter two dates within 30 days to limit its
      search. To display a single day, set both dates equal to that
      day.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The <emphasis>Trade Calendar</emphasis> opens in
      <emphasis>Standard View</emphasis> by default. If you clicked a specific
      day, the main part of the screen shows all the events of that day. If
      you clicked a month name, it shows all the events of the month.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">In <emphasis>Milestone
      </emphasis><emphasis>V</emphasis><emphasis>iew</emphasis>, the search
      can span over a period of up to three months. Key dates are not grouped
      by date, but rather by product and then product type. The date range can
      be set in the search criteria fields at the top of the screen. To return
      to <emphasis>Standard view</emphasis>, click <emphasis>Switch to
      Standard View</emphasis>, below the calendar.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>List of Events</title>

      <para role="TEXT">As usual with lists, you can enter search criteria in a group of
      fields at the top of the list and click <emphasis>Search</emphasis>, to
      display the records that match these criteria.</para>

      <para role="TEXT"><emphasis>List of Events</emphasis> displays the following fields,
      depending on the type of view selected:</para>

      <informaltable frame="all">
        <tgroup cols="3">
          <colspec colname="column-1" colwidth="1860*" />

          <colspec colname="column-2" colwidth="2028*" />

          <colspec colname="column-3" colwidth="4968*" />

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry>Field</entry>

              <entry>Displayed in</entry>

              <entry>Description</entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">
              <guilabel>Reference</guilabel> </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Both <emphasis>Standard
              View</emphasis> and <emphasis>Milestone
              View</emphasis></para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">!!! 1. To be
              added!!!</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel>Date</guilabel>
              </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Both <emphasis>Standard
              View</emphasis> and <emphasis>Milestone
              View</emphasis></para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Indicates the day of the
              event.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel>Type</guilabel>
              </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Both <emphasis>Standard
              View</emphasis> and <emphasis>Milestone
              View</emphasis></para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Shows either the product
              code, if it is a key date of a transaction record, or the key
              word <emphasis>Ev</emphasis>. if the event is added manually to
              the calendar.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel>Title</guilabel>
              </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Both <emphasis>Standard
              View</emphasis> and <emphasis>Milestone
              View</emphasis></para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Provides a description of the
              key date, if it involves a transaction record (such as
              <emphasis>Issue Date, Expiry Date, Maturity Date, Last Shipment
              Date, Application Date</emphasis>, etc.). Else, it displays the
              title chosen by the user while entering the details of the
              custom event.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel>User
              Name</guilabel> </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"><emphasis>Standard
              View</emphasis><emphasis> </emphasis>only</para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">For a static event, it
              indicates the name of the event's owner.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel>Entity</guilabel>
              </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"><emphasis>Milestone
              View</emphasis><emphasis> </emphasis>only</para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">!!! 2. To be
              added!!!</para></entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable>

      <para role="TEXT">Click <emphasis>Search</emphasis> to displays the list of events
      based on the above criteria.</para>
    </section>
  </section>
</chapter>
