<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>Managing Funds Transfer</title>

  <info />

  <para role="TEXT">This chapter helps you with processing funds transfer, making payments
  from your accounts, and performing transfer inquiries using Opics
  Portal.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Transferring Funds between Accounts</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Using Opics Portal, you can transfer funds from one account to
    another, from a list of available accounts.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In the portal <emphasis>Home page</emphasis>, click <emphasis>Fund
    Transfer </emphasis>and then under <emphasis>Initiation</emphasis> select
    <emphasis>Transfer</emphasis> to create an internal fund transfer request.
    You can select the debit amount and the date for the transfer.</para>

    <note>
      <para role="TEXT">: If no value date is specified, then it takes the current branch
      processing date (CASH).</para>
    </note>

    <para role="TEXT">If the call and notice account is denominated in different
    currencies, the underlying FX deal price is requested based on the
    customer, currencies of the accounts, transfer amount, and value date. The
    FX price is displayed on the entry screen.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">On successful completion of the transfer, the portal displays the
    transaction details, debit and credit deal reference numbers, and
    (optionally) the underlying FX deal number.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Making Payments from Accounts</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Using the portal, you can make payments from one particular account,
    from the list of call and notice accounts.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In the portal <emphasis>Home page</emphasis>, click <emphasis>Fund
    Transfer </emphasis>and then under <emphasis>Initiation</emphasis> select
    <emphasis>Payment</emphasis> to create an outgoing fund transfer request.
    You can specify the amount, value date, and the currency of the
    payment.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">If the payment currency specified is in the account currency then an
    underlying FX price request is performed based on the two currencies, the
    customer of the account, the value date, and amount of the payment. The FX
    price is displayed on the entry screen.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">You can either select from a list of standard and usual settlement
    instructions or can enter the instructions manually.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">On successful completion of the payment, the portal displays the
    transaction details, debit and credit deal reference numbers.</para>

    <note>
      <para role="TEXT">: Payments from a call and notice liability account generates a
      decrease to that account, whereas that from an asset account generates
      an increase to that account.</para>
    </note>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Making Payments with Transfers</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Opics Portal also facilitates to make payments with transfers for
    the call and notice accounts.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">In the portal <emphasis>Home page</emphasis>, click <emphasis>Fund
    Transfer </emphasis>and then under <emphasis>Initiation</emphasis> select
    <emphasis>Payment with Transfer</emphasis> to create an internal and
    outgoing fund transfer request.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Here, you can create an unbalanced transfer where the debut amount
    is greater than the credit amount. If you select to perform one of these
    transactions, then the remaining balance is made available for the payment
    as explained above.</para>

    <tip>
      <para role="TEXT">: The debit amount cannot be less than the credit amount.</para>
    </tip>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Funds Transfer Inquiry</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Opics Portal provides information about the status, the details, and
    the history of fund transfers initiated by the user. The list of transfers
    is confined to those transactions entered on the current processing
    date.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">You can make inquiries on fund transfers as follows:</para>

    <orderedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">From the <emphasis>Main Menu</emphasis>, click <emphasis>Fund
        Transfer</emphasis> and then click
        <emphasis>F</emphasis><emphasis>T</emphasis><emphasis>Inquiry</emphasis>.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">In the <emphasis>Ccy</emphasis> field, specify the currency of
        the transfer.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Select the <emphasis>Output Format</emphasis> to display on
        <emphasis>Screen</emphasis>, or save the results in
        <emphasis>CSV</emphasis> or <emphasis>Spreadsheet</emphasis>.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Click <emphasis>Search</emphasis> to retrieve a list of records
        displaying funds transfer in the specified currency.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Click the <emphasis>System ID</emphasis> of a record to view the
        details of a particular transfer.</para>
      </listitem>
    </orderedlist>

    <tip>
      <para role="TEXT">: You can use wildcards in your search string. For example, type
      *MYTEXT* to search for the items containing the MYTEXT string.</para>
    </tip>

    <para role="TEXT">Moreover, you can also filter or sort the information returned from
    the portal on a multi or single column basis.</para>
  </section>
</chapter>
