<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>Getting Started</title>

  <para role="TEXT">This chapter introduces the Web interface through which
  you use <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Welcome and Log In</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When you connect to <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> , you see the Welcome/Login
    page.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Enter your user ID, password and company name provided,
    then click Login.</para>

    <note>
      <para role="TEXT">First time login displays the 'Registration' page.
      Read the terms and conditions, enter any required details for
      registration, and click on <guibutton>Register</guibutton> to continue
      further.</para>
    </note>
  </section>

  <section id="ForgotUsernamePassword" role="ITEM">
    <title>Forgot Username or Password?</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The 'Forgot Username or Password?' link under Login
    button enables you to reset the Password or retrieve your Username.<figure>
        <title>Forgot Username or Password?</title>

        <mediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="images/forgotpassword.png" width="100mm"/>
          </imageobject>
        </mediaobject>
      </figure></para>

    <para>Click on the 'Forgot Username or Password?' link to open the Reset
    Password / Retrieve Username form. Ensure that you are on the right tab to
    Reset Password or Retrieve username and fill all the details. The
    individual fields of each tab are described in the following
    sections.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Reset Password</title>

      <para role="TEXT">This tab enables you to reset password for your
      username. The following steps guide you to reset password.</para>

      <para><orderedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>Enter the mandatory fields <userinput>Corporate
            ID</userinput>, <userinput>Username</userinput> and
            <userinput>E-mail</userinput> ID with valid data.<figure>
                <title>Forgot Password</title>

                <mediaobject>
                  <imageobject>
                    <imagedata fileref="images/forgotpwdnxtpg.png"
                               width="75mm"/>
                  </imageobject>
                </mediaobject>
              </figure></para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>Click on the reCAPTCHA checkbox to validate that you are a
            human.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>Click on Next</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>Enter the the OTP (One Time Password) that you receive on
            your E-mail address on authentication page.<note>
                <para>The OTP is valid only for 2 minutes, incase the time
                period expires the following message is displayed "The OTP is
                expired. Kindly regenerate the OTP and try again".</para>
              </note><figure>
                <title>Authentication</title>

                <mediaobject>
                  <imageobject>
                    <imagedata fileref="images/forgotpwdauth.png" width="75mm"/>
                  </imageobject>
                </mediaobject>
              </figure></para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>Upon successful authentication, you are directed to 'Change
            Password' screen; enter the new password and Submit.</para>
          </listitem>
        </orderedlist></para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Retrieve Username</title>

      <para role="TEXT">This section enables you to retrieve username. Follow
      the steps given below to retrieve username.</para>

      <para><orderedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>Enter the mandatory fields <userinput>Corporate
            ID</userinput> and <userinput>E-mail</userinput> ID with valid
            data.<figure>
                <title>Retrieve Username</title>

                <mediaobject>
                  <imageobject>
                    <imagedata fileref="images/retrieveuser.png" width="75mm"/>
                  </imageobject>
                </mediaobject>
              </figure></para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>Click on the reCAPTCHA checkbox to validate that you are a
            human.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para>Click on Next, upon successful validation of data entered by
            you a success message is displayed.<mediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="images/retrieveusersuccess.png"
                             width="75mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </mediaobject></para>
          </listitem>
        </orderedlist></para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>The <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Client Home Page</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Once logged in, the Client Home page will be
    displayed.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Each of the sections of the <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Client Home page are listed
    here:</para>

    <orderedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">The <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
        xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>
        Banner</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">The Toolbar</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Finastra Feature Bookmarks</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Bank News</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Outstanding Amounts</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Recent Pending Transactions</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Recent Notifications</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">The Calendar</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">DHL Tracking System</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Rates</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Account Balances</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Call and Notice Accounts</para>
      </listitem>
    </orderedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">In many cases, there are multiple methods of navigating
    to specific functions or options. Some of these methods will be discussed
    in this guide.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>The Banner</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
      xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> banner
      is the same on every page, with the Finastra or bank's logo on the left
      side.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">To its right side are the following details available
      on the banner: <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Bank Business Date and Timezone - This is
            available only when the property show.bank.datetime is set to
            'true'. The user can set this property to true when the bank
            timezone and user timezone are different.<note>
                <para>All the business validations and dates like Expiry Date
                and others are calculated based on Bank's timezone.</para>
              </note></para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Last login details</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Contact Helpdesk access link</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist></para>

      <para>The banner header is followed by the following three
      sections:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">The user login name and company name.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Manage profile link (followed by your login name
          and company name) that allows the user profile, Password, and
          Security questions to be changed:</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">My Pending link to view and perform action on
          tasks requiring your authorisation.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Logout button to log out of the <xi:include
          href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
          xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>.</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">As the banner is displayed on all pages, these options
      can be selected at any time.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>The Toolbar</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Below the banner on the Home page, is the Tool bar.
      The Tool bar is displayed on all pages of the <xi:include
      href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Client Portal.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The Tool bar provides links to the functions and
      features of the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
      xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> that
      the user has access to, through their roles and permissions. The first
      icon displayed on the Tool bar, is the Home button <inlinemediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_home.gif" width="5mm"/>
          </imageobject>
        </inlinemediaobject>. Click on this button while displaying any page
      in the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> will return the user to the
      Home page. Following the Home button are four lists, providing links to
      the features and functions available in the <xi:include
      href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> client Portal.</para>

      <note>
        <para role="TEXT">The availability of the menus and their functions,
        is dependent on the permissions assigned to the user. Only those menus
        containing functions the user is authorised to use will be
        displayed.</para>
      </note>

      <para role="TEXT"><variablelist>
          <varlistentry>
            <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Account
            Services</guimenuitem></term>

            <listitem>
              <para role="TEXT">Enables to view Account summaries and
              statements, view Transaction lists, inquire on and execute Batch
              processing, produce reports, list transactions that require
              authorization within your authority level, Term Deposits and
              Loans, and view advices and notifications received from the
              Bank.</para>
            </listitem>
          </varlistentry>

          <varlistentry>
            <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Cash
            Services</guimenuitem></term>

            <listitem>
              <para role="TEXT">Enables to make payments to and transfer money
              to local and external accounts, create money orders and cheques
              for payment, create remittance advices, upload files into the
              <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
              xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>, and create Bulk
              Orders for payment or collection of orders.</para>
            </listitem>
          </varlistentry>

          <varlistentry>
            <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">SCF
            Services</guimenuitem></term>

            <listitem>
              <para role="TEXT">Creates Invoicing, Purchase Orders and Credit
              Notes.</para>
            </listitem>
          </varlistentry>

          <varlistentry>
            <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Trade
            Services</guimenuitem></term>

            <listitem>
              <para role="TEXT">Creates Import and Export Letters of Credit,
              Import and Export Collections, Bankers and Shipping Guarantees,
              Finance requests, and inward remittances.</para>
            </listitem>
          </varlistentry>

          <varlistentry>
            <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Lending
            Services</guimenuitem></term>

            <listitem>
              <para role="TEXT">Create Initial Drawdown, Loan Increase, Adhoc
              Payments, Remittance Instructions, Track documents (only
              listing), Loan Repricing (only Comprehensive), Borrower bills
              (only listing) and Loan history.</para>
            </listitem>
          </varlistentry>

          <varlistentry>
            <term><guimenuitem moreinfo="none">Treasury
            Services</guimenuitem></term>

            <listitem>
              <para role="TEXT">Processes Foreign Exchange (FX) instruments
              such as Deals, Wires and Transfers, and Certificate of Deposit
              (CD); creates, maintains, and submits the FX Spot, FX Forward,
              and FX Window Forward trade requests; adds, edits, and releases
              bank payment instructions; processes payments, internal fund
              transfers, and external fund transfers; and initiates a CD,
              attaches instructions, and allows to rollover a CD.</para>
            </listitem>
          </varlistentry>

          <varlistentry>
            <term><guimenuitem
            moreinfo="none">Administration</guimenuitem></term>

            <listitem>
              <para role="TEXT">Manages the setup and use of the <xi:include
              href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
              xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> at the customer or
              Entity level. Most users will only be able to access the Change
              Profile service (also accessible from the banner). Other
              services are only available to client administrator, and are
              described in the Client Administrator Guide. This item is only
              available to Client administrator and will not be covered in
              this guide. For more information, see the Client Administrator
              Guide.</para>
            </listitem>
          </varlistentry>
        </variablelist></para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Finastra Feature Bookmarks</title>

      <para role="TEXT">To the far right of the toolbar, a bookmark icon is
      available on all screens, to allow convenient access to personalise
      shortcuts as required.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Bookmarks can be created from most functions and
      options within the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
      xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>. To
      create a bookmark, enter the required function or option and click on
      the "<emphasis>Add Bookmark</emphasis>" link at the bottom, left of the
      screen.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Existing bookmarks will always be shown at the bottom
      left hand side of any function screen, and can be used from any screen
      in the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>, as a direct link to
      another function.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">To remove a bookmark, move the mouse over the link and
      click on the circled 'X'.</para>

      <note>
        <para role="TEXT">Bookmarks is available for customer user functions
        (<literal>Account Services</literal> , <literal>Cash Services, Loan
        Services, Treasury Services</literal> and <literal>Trade
        Services</literal> tabs) and not for administrator functions
        (<literal>Administration</literal> tab).</para>
      </note>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Bank News</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Beneath the list of personalised shortcuts, is the
      News portlet (an application running within the page)</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The News Portlet is maintained and updated by the
      bank, providing news and information that the bank wishes to pass on to
      their customers.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Outstanding Amounts</title>

      <para role="TEXT">In the center of the screen, below the Tool bar, is a
      list of transactions that have not yet been completed and have
      outstanding amounts assigned to them.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">These are grouped according to the entities assigned
      to the user's company, and provide an immediate summary of outstanding
      amounts for each transaction that has been entered into and approved.
      Clicking on any to the list headings will allow the list to be sorted
      according to that column value.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Recent Pending Transactions</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Further down on the Home page, under the overall
      heading of 'Trade Events', is a list of all pending (or incomplete)
      transaction that have been started but not completed or submitted by the
      user.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This list shows the most recent pending transactions
      initiated within your company (for any product and any type of
      transaction, whether initiation, amendment or message). Pending means in
      Incomplete (Draft) or Uncontrolled (Unsigned) status, and hence not yet
      sent to the bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Each entry shows the transaction's System ID, followed
      by the transaction type (<type>New</type>, <type>Amend</type>, or
      <type>Update</type>/<type>Message</type>). Click the System ID to open
      the transaction record in the appropriate mode for its status. That is,
      a transaction that only needs to be signed opens in non-editable mode,
      whereas an incomplete record opens in the edit form for its transaction
      type.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">To avoid over-crowding your home page, the list shows,
      by default, only the 5 most recent such transactions (sorted by input
      date). This can be changed by setting a different value in the relevant
      configuration file.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Items can only be deleted by listing them in the
      Inquiry function for the specific type of function.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Recent Notifications</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Beneath the list of Pending transactions, is a list of
      recent notification. Notifications are messages from the bank,
      approving, rejecting, or querying transactions that have been submitted
      by the customer.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This list shows the most recent notifications sent to
      your company from the bank's Trade Services. Each item in the list shows
      the System ID of the transaction, The Bank Reference number, the type, a
      time stamp showing the system date of the server when the bank sent the
      message, and it's status. A green or red status by an entry shows
      whether the bank has acknowledged or rejected it.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click the System ID to open the transaction in history
      mode. From that page, a more detailed popup window detailing the event
      can be launched.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Like for the Recent Pending Transactions, the list
      shows, by default, only the 5 most recent such notifications. This can
      be changed by setting a different value in the relevant configuration
      file.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Balance Alerts</title>

      <para role="TEXT">This is a summary of all the balance alerts for
      current date. The alerts shown are those for the user account. Click on
      <guibutton>Today</guibutton> to display a detailed list of alarms for
      the current date, and click on <guibutton>Account Balance
      Alert</guibutton> to display a detailed list of all the alerts.Click on
      <guibutton>Today</guibutton>/<guibutton>Account Balance
      Alert</guibutton> takes the user to Review Alerts Screen (Inquiry
      Balances and Transactions Review Alerts).</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Here is a sample view of the alerts.</para>

      <para role="TEXT"><inlinemediaobject>
          <imageobject>
            <imagedata fileref="../images/user_client-fig.alerts.gif"
                       width="35mm"/>
          </imageobject>
        </inlinemediaobject></para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>The Calendar</title>

      <para role="TEXT">To the right hand side of the screen, the Events
      Calendar is displayed. The <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
      xpointer="ent_Calendar" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> is
      used to track the events related to transactions initiated by your
      company through the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
      xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>,
      together with any custom events (like appointments or reminders) related
      to the activity of your company, in much the same way that you would
      through a shared electronic calendar.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This module enables you to monitor key dates related
      to the products handled by the system, as well as adding your own custom
      events or alerts, turning your <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
      xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> page
      into an automated and customised scheduler.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The calendar appears on your home page, together with
      today's events. It is also accessible as a full screen application where
      events can be displayed by day, month or by type over a longer period of
      time in the Milestones View. For any event related to an existing
      transaction, a dedicated link gives you access to the transaction
      details and history through a single mouse click.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The following events will be displayed in the
      calendar:<itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Public events added through the Add event below
            the calendar or clicking on a date in the calendar</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Private events for the current user added
            through the Add event below the calendar or clicking on a date in
            the calendar</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Some business dates of the transaction in the
            <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
            xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Import. These
            include:</para>

            <itemizedlist>
              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Letter of Credit: issue date, expiry date,
                last shipment date, maturity date, amendment date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Export Letter of Credit: issue date,
                expiry date, last shipment date, maturity date, amendment
                date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Shipping Guarantee: issue date, expiry
                date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Financing Request: issue date, maturity
                date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Banker's Guarantee: issue date, expiry
                date, amendment date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Export Collection: application date,
                maturity date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Import Collection: application date,
                maturity date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Inward Remittance: remittance date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Fund Transfer: value date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Factoring: issue date Invoice: issue date,
                due date</para>
              </listitem>

              <listitem>
                <para role="TEXT">- Invoice Payable: issue date, due
                date</para>
              </listitem>
            </itemizedlist>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist></para>

      <section role="ITEM">
        <title>Calendar Component</title>

        <para role="TEXT">This component displays the calendar itself. It
        displays a calendar for the month, the current business date in your
        time zone highlighted, and serves as a table of contents to access the
        details of any date. Click a day to see a full page view of that day's
        events. Click the month name to see a full-page view of the month's
        events. Click the arrows around the month name to see the previous and
        following months.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">Days associated with key dates are automatically
        highlighted with a specific background colour. With this visual
        information, it is easy to detect right from the home page the key
        transactional events taking place during the month.</para>
      </section>

      <section role="ITEM">
        <title>Today's Events</title>

        <para role="TEXT">This list is a summary of all the events of the
        current day. Events shown are those for your company's transactions,
        plus any custom events manually added by any of your company's
        users.</para>

        <para role="TEXT">The transactions displayed are the records bearing a
        key date equal to the current business date. Click the heading
        <guibutton>Today</guibutton> to display a more detailed list of
        events..</para>

        <para role="TEXT">Click <guilabel moreinfo="none">Add Event</guilabel>
        to add an event to the calendar. An event can be <type>Private</type>
        (only be seen by you), or <type>Public</type> (shared by all users in
        your company).</para>

        <para role="TEXT">In addition, Alerts can be added to inform
        customers, entities and/or users to specific system events. Alerts can
        only be added by an authorised user, through the Alerts Maintenance
        Function in the Services menu. This feature is described in the Client
        Administration Guide.</para>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>DHL Tracking System</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The DHL tracking system list is a link to the DHL site
      to enable the user to track reports, notifications and/or goods, sent by
      the user via DHL couriers and transport services.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Clicking on this link will open a new tab, and leave
      the <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> open for later use.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Rates</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The Rates list is displayed on the left and at the
      bottom of the page.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This list displays current buying and selling rates
      against the Singapore dollar, for the most common currencies. The rates
      specified are maintained by the Bank Administrators.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Account Balances</title>

      <para role="TEXT">The Account Balances list normally appears near the
      top and center of the page.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This list displays the current balance of all accounts
      defined for your user account. It provides a summarised view of your
      accounts such as current account, loan account, fixed deposits and so
      on. The columns have data for Account, Account Type, Currency, Account
      Number and Balance.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click on the <guilabel>Account</guilabel> link and the
      Account Statement screen is displayed for most of the product types,
      except for Term Deposit accounts, which displays an Account Details
      popup.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Call and Notice Accounts</title>

      <para role="TEXT">All the Call and Notice accounts belonging to a
      customer with the opening balance is displayed in the
      <emphasis>Home</emphasis> page. The opening balance is calculated at the
      end of the day in the treasury back office and sent to the <xi:include
      href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> database. Selecting an
      account from the Home page displays the account activity page.</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Lists</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Many functions display a page that lists relevant
    transactions. These list pages have many things in common:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">You can enter search criteria in a group of fields
        at the top of the page and click <guibutton
        role="bold">Search</guibutton> , to make the list show only records
        that match these criteria. These fields represent the most important
        fields in the transaction record, as do the columns in the
        table.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">You can use wild cards in these fields. The wild
        card character is an asterisk (*). You can use it anywhere in a
        field.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">The search is not case sensitive.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">On pages where the list might be very long - for
        example, if there are many transactions - the list is not displayed
        until you have entered the search criteria and clicked <guibutton
        role="bold">Search</guibutton>. Until manually specified, the list
        will display "No records found", just as it would if there actually
        were no records in the list.. Enter an asterisk in any of the search
        fields to get the entire list.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">If your company has entities defined in its profile,
        then a column and a search criterion field for <emphasis
        role="bold">Entity</emphasis> appear in addition to the columns and
        fields mentioned in the individual chapters.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Each heading of a column can be clicked on, to make
        a triangular icon appear, which in turn can be clicked again, to sort
        the list on that column, in ascending or descending order.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">In most lists, the individually entry in the list
        can be clicked, to process the transaction shown in that row.
        Depending on the list, transactions can sometimes be edited, viewed,
        deleted, or an amendment request created. Some lists allow the item to
        be clicked anywhere in the row, while others require the
        <guibutton>System ID</guibutton> column to be clicked, while others
        have icons for each actions. Details of list requirements are given in
        the sections for the individual functions.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Forms</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Most functions display an input form, either immediately
    you click the function or after you click a row in a list displayed by the
    function. These forms have many things in common:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Near the top right of a form, you'll see a
        free-floating menu on a coloured background, with the entries
        <guimenuitem>Show Form Summary</guimenuitem> and <guimenuitem>Top
        <inlinemediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="../images/Form_Summary.GIF"
                         role="CHAR_RADIO" width="40mm"/>
            </imageobject>
          </inlinemediaobject></guimenuitem>. This menu stays put as you
        scroll up and down the form. Clicking <guibutton>Top</guibutton> takes
        the display back to the top of the form. Clicking <guimenuitem>Show
        Form Summary</guimenuitem> displays a menu of all the section headings
        in the form. These can be clicked to display the required section of
        the form.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Fields with a <inlinemediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_glass.gif"/>
            </imageobject>
          </inlinemediaobject> (magnifying glass) icon to the right, indicate
        that by clicking the icon, a popup list of accepted values will be
        displayed. Click a value to insert it in the field. This is most often
        used for currency fields.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">If a field has a <inlinemediaobject>
            <imageobject>
              <imagedata fileref="../images/icon_phrases.gif"/>
            </imageobject>
          </inlinemediaobject> icon by it, clicking the icon will display
        popup list of predefined phrases. Click a phrase to insert it in the
        field. These fields can usually be edited further. This facility is
        most often used for free-format fields such as <guilabel>Other
        Information</guilabel> fields.</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">In some date fields, you can enter the date in two
        ways:</para>

        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Select the first option button to enter the
            required date. Click the field and select the date from the
            calendar.</para>
          </listitem>

          <listitem>
            <para role="TEXT">Select the second option button to enter a
            length of time. Insert the number of days/weeks/months/years in
            the first field. Select from the dropdown list:
            <literal>Days</literal>, <literal>Weeks</literal>,
            <literal>Months</literal> or <literal>Years</literal>.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>

    <para role="TEXT">This documentation describes each input form in detail,
    with a table describing each control (field, button, etc). The middle
    column in these tables contains symbols showing what type each control is,
    as follows:</para>

    <informaltable role="TEXT">
      <tgroup cols="2">
        <tbody>
          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_info.gif"
                             role="CHAR_INFO" width="4mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

            <entry>Read-only field</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_excla.gif"
                             role="CHAR_EXCLA" width="2mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject></para></entry>

            <entry>Input field</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_excla.gif"
                             role="CHAR_EXCLA" width="2mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject> <inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_arrow.gif"
                             role="CHAR_ARROW" width="2mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

            <entry>Input field with dropdown list to select from</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_excla.gif"
                             role="CHAR_EXCLA" width="2mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject><inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_action.gif"
                             role="CHAR_ACTION" width="3mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

            <entry>Input field with button to display a popup list to select
            from</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_action.gif"
                             role="CHAR_ACTION" width="3mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

            <entry>Button</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"><inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_check.gif"
                             role="CHAR_CHECK" width="3mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject></para></entry>

            <entry>Check box</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_radio.gif"
                             role="CHAR_RADIO" width="3mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

            <entry>Set of option buttons</entry>
          </row>

          <row>
            <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <inlinemediaobject>
                <imageobject>
                  <imagedata fileref="../images/char_tab.gif"
                             role="CHAR_RADIO" width="4mm"/>
                </imageobject>
              </inlinemediaobject> </para></entry>

            <entry>Information Tab</entry>
          </row>
        </tbody>
      </tgroup>
    </informaltable>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Date and Amount Formats</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When entering a date in a date field, you can enter it
    in the form <replaceable>DD/MM/YYYY</replaceable> or
    <replaceable>DDMMYY</replaceable> if your locale is for instance France,
    or in the form <replaceable>MM/DD/YYYY</replaceable> or
    <replaceable>MMDDYY</replaceable> if your locale is for instance the
    USA..</para>

    <para role="TEXT"><informalexample>
        <para role="TEXT">For example, entering <literal
        moreinfo="none">180401</literal> produces a display of <literal
        moreinfo="none">18/04/2001</literal>, which in a French locale
        corresponds to 18th April 2001.</para>
      </informalexample></para>

    <para role="TEXT">When you enter an amount, the system automatically
    formats the value entered according to the currency selected. You can
    either enter the amount using the decimal and group delimiters of your
    locale (for example, respectively [,] and [space] for France, or [.] and
    [,] for Singapore), or directly as a series of digits.</para>

    <para role="TEXT"><informalexample>
        <para role="TEXT">For example, <literal
        moreinfo="none">123456.00</literal> in a Singaporean locale produces a
        display of <literal moreinfo="none">123,456.00</literal> if the
        currency involved is associated with 2 decimal places.</para>
      </informalexample></para>

    <para>The following table lists the allowed characters for various Field
    Types <informaltable role="TEXT">
        <tgroup cols="3">
          <colspec colname="c1" colwidth="181*"/>

          <colspec colwidth="109*"/>

          <colspec colname="c2" colwidth="710*"/>

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Field Types</para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Definition</para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">Description</para></entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel
              moreinfo="none">alpha </guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">only
              letters</para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">A B C D E F G H I J K L M
              N O P Q R S T U V W X Y Z a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s
              t u v w x y z</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Numeric </guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">only digits</para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
              9</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Amount</guilabel></para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> numbers with decimal
              separator </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 .
              </para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Alphanumeric</guilabel> </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> digits + letters
              </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"/></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> <guilabel
              moreinfo="none">Alphanumeric + swift X special
              characters</guilabel> </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT"> digits + letters + swift
              X special characters </para></entry>

              <entry valign="top"><para role="TEXT">space ' ( ) + , - . / : ?
              A B C D E F G H I J K L M N O P Q R S T U V W X Y Z a b c d e f
              g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
              </para></entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable></para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Forward and Back Browser Buttons Behaviour</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When you use a Browser's Forward and Back buttons, the
    browser's default behaviour is displayed and <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> doesn't provide any
    customised messages.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Antivirus Scanning Service</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This service provides an interface from <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> to an antivirus scanner of
    your company's choice. You can scan any attachment for viruses before
    uploading it from any transaction screen in <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/>.</para>

    <note>
      <para role="TEXT">This service is enabled by the <xi:include
      href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"/> Administrator.</para>
    </note>
  </section>
</chapter>
