<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>Portal Functions</title>

  <para role="TEXT">This chapter describes the common functions performed by Opics Portal.
  For each transaction type (or product), the portal provides a module that
  enables you to initiate, amend, and monitor transactions on behalf of your
  company. These modules provide similar set of functions as described in this
  chapter.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">For basic features common to all modules, such as basic terminology
  and the behavior of lists, see <emphasis>About This Manual</emphasis> and
  <emphasis>Getting Started</emphasis> section.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Portlets</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The <emphasis>Recent Pending Transactions</emphasis> list within the
    <emphasis>Trade Events</emphasis> portlet on your
    <emphasis>H</emphasis><emphasis>ome page</emphasis> shows recent events in
    all modules. This portlet is provided by the <emphasis>Trade
    Calendar</emphasis> module.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Validation and Submission</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Several types of validation are done when you fill in an input
    form.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">First, each field is validated as you enter it. Errors that can be
    detected by local validation of the field are indicated by a popup message
    as soon as the cursor leaves the field.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">When you have completed a form and you click on
    <emphasis>Request</emphasis> or <emphasis>Submit</emphasis>, the form is
    checked to ensure that all mandatory fields are filled in. If not, you get
    an error message and the first uncompleted mandatory field is
    highlighted.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Once all mandatory fields are filled in,
    <emphasis>Request</emphasis> or <emphasis>Submit</emphasis> sends the form
    to the back-office software for more detailed validation. If any errors
    are detected, you get a message box with the text <emphasis>"A validation
    error has occurred"</emphasis> and a <emphasis>More&gt;</emphasis>
    link.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Click <emphasis>More&gt;</emphasis> to see a list of the errors. The
    first few lines may be general error messages such as <emphasis>"Failed to
    execute request"</emphasis> and <emphasis>"Failed to validate
    ..."</emphasis>. The actual error messages then follow.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">At certain points in filling in a form, you can click a button (for
    example, <emphasis>Search</emphasis> on some forms) to cause an action for
    which data has to be sent to the back-office software. This too gives you
    the message box if any errors are detected.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">If you clicked <emphasis>Request</emphasis> or
    <emphasis>Submit</emphasis> and no errors are found, the back-office
    software assigns a bank reference to your transaction. You get the Submit
    <emphasis>transaction</emphasis><emphasis>-type</emphasis> Initiation
    page, which displays the message <emphasis>"Your
    </emphasis><emphasis>transaction</emphasis><emphasis>-type with Bank
    Reference number has been successfully submitted"</emphasis>.</para>

    <tip>
      <para role="TEXT"><emphasis></emphasis>Ensure that you make a note of the bank
      reference number.</para>
    </tip>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Main Menu</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The Main Menu, located on the left side, provides a list of modules
    and features in Opics Portal. The items in this menu depend on which
    modules your account has permissions for.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Module Functions</title>

    <para role="TEXT">You enter the submenu of a module by clicking the corresponding
    module on the <emphasis>M</emphasis><emphasis>ain menu</emphasis> on your
    <emphasis>H</emphasis><emphasis>ome page</emphasis>. On the menu for each
    module are the functions listed in this section.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">All the functions in these modules handle only transactions of the
    type handled by the current module. In many cases the name of the function
    or set of functions is followed by the name of the asset type handled by
    the module. For example, in the FX module the menu item shown here as
    'Inquiry' is <emphasis>FX Inquiry</emphasis>.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Where it is necessary to include the transaction type we call it
    <emphasis>trade-type</emphasis>. Thus, in the Term Deposit module,
    <emphasis>transaction</emphasis><emphasis>-</emphasis><emphasis>type</emphasis>
    is Term Deposit. The individual functions are described in the rest of
    this chapter.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Common Functions</title>

      <para role="TEXT"><emphasis>Initiation</emphasis>: Provides a set of functions for
      creating a request to initiate a transaction, and submitting it to the
      bank.</para>

      <para role="TEXT"><emphasis>Message to Bank</emphasis>: Provides a set of functions
      for making amendments to a transaction and managing standing
      instructions for your transactions.</para>

      <para role="TEXT"><emphasis>Unsigned</emphasis>: Function to display a list of your
      company's pending transactions; that is, those that are have Draft or
      Unsigned status. You can open transactions to edit or submit
      them.</para>

      <para role="TEXT"><emphasis>Inquiry</emphasis>: Function to display a list of your
      company's files, so you can view their details and optionally print a
      hard copy of these details.</para>

      <para role="TEXT"><emphasis>Maintenance</emphasis>: Provides a set of functions to
      carry out maintenance tasks, including deleting outdated
      transactions.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Operations</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Most functions display a form, with buttons to click and complete
      the transactions. Some of the common buttons are given below.</para>

      <informaltable frame="all">
        <tgroup cols="2">
          <colspec colname="column-1" colwidth="2668*" />

          <colspec colname="column-2" colwidth="6080*" />

          <thead>
            <row>
              <entry>Button</entry>

              <entry>Operation</entry>
            </row>
          </thead>

          <tbody>
            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">
              <guibutton>Request</guibutton> </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Initiates a transaction with
              the bank requesting for information.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"> <guibutton>Clear</guibutton>
              </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Clears all the fields in the
              form</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">
              <guibutton>Search</guibutton> </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Performs a look-up based on
              the search criteria specified in the form. Displays the result
              if the criteria matched. Else, displays a message indicating
              that no result is retrieved.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"> <guibutton>Save</guibutton>
              </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Stores the transaction as a
              draft, so that you or another user can continue to work on it
              later. No validation is done. It is not sent to the bank.</para>
              <para role="TEXT">Not present on <emphasis>Unsigned</emphasis> forms, as
              these cannot be edited.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">
              <guibutton>Submit</guibutton> </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Sends the transaction to the
              bank. The form is validated, as described in section
              <emphasis>Validation</emphasis><emphasis> and
              Submission</emphasis>.</para> <para role="TEXT">If you do not have
              sufficient permissions (for example, to handle the amount you
              have requested), the transaction is not sent and an error
              message is displayed. Its status changes to
              <emphasis>Unsigned</emphasis>.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">
              <guibutton>Template</guibutton> </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Saves the transaction as a
              template, so that you or another user can base new transactions
              on it. As no validation is done for it, it is not sent to the
              bank.</para> <para role="TEXT">Present in <emphasis>New
              </emphasis><emphasis>transaction</emphasis><emphasis>-type</emphasis>
              forms.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">
              <guibutton>Cancel</guibutton> </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Discards the transaction and
              quits the form without saving it, and returns to the
              <emphasis>Main menu</emphasis> of the module.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"> <guibutton>Help</guibutton>
              </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Launches a new window
              displaying the online help.</para></entry>
            </row>

            <row>
              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT"> <guibutton>Delete selected
              transactions</guibutton> </para></entry>

              <entry colsep="1" rowsep="1"><para role="TEXT">Removes the selected
              transaction from the database.</para></entry>
            </row>
          </tbody>
        </tgroup>
      </informaltable>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Initiating Transactions</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The initiation menu contains functions for creating a transaction
    and submitting it to the bank.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>From Scratch</title>

      <para role="TEXT">You can create a transaction from scratch and optionally send it
      to the bank. You can alternatively save it as a template, from which
      such initiations can be created.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays the New
      <emphasis>transaction</emphasis><emphasis>-type</emphasis> (for example,
      New Loan) input form. You use this form to create your initiation and
      validate it, save it as a draft, save it as a template, or submit it to
      the bank (if you have sufficient authority).</para>

      <para role="TEXT">The input form is different for each transaction type. For
      detailed descriptions of these input forms, see the chapters for the
      individual transaction types.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Retrieve Draft</title>

      <para role="TEXT">You can continue working on a transaction that you or another user
      have already started and saved. This function displays a list of Draft
      or Unsigned transactions created by users in your company.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click in the <emphasis>System ID</emphasis> column to open the
      initiation in a New
      <emphasis>transaction</emphasis><emphasis>-type</emphasis> input form
      for further editing, after which you can again validate it, save it as a
      draft, save it as a template, or submit it to the bank (if you have
      sufficient authority).</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Message to Bank</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This menu contains the following functions.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Standing Instructions</title>

      <para role="TEXT">You can view and modify standing instruction for your
      transactions.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>From Existing Transaction-type</title>

      <para role="TEXT">You can view and modify existing transactions and submit them to
      the bank, for example, you can modify the value date of your FX
      transactions or split the amount of a particular FX deal. Below is the
      detailed description of modifying a transaction.</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Inquiry and Maintenance</title>

    <para role="TEXT">This section describes the inquiry and maintenance functions of the
    portal.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">First we describe the <emphasis>Output Format</emphasis> field,
    common to several of these functions.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Output Format</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Some functions in this part of the menu have a feature to let you
      choose the destination and format of the lists they display.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Below the search criteria fields is an <emphasis>Output
      Format</emphasis> field, where you select the destination and format
      from a drop-down list:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Screen (Default)</para>

          <para role="TEXT">Displays the list on the same web page, in the normal list
          format.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">CSV</para>

          <para role="TEXT">Downloads the report to your machine as Comma-Separated Values
          file.</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Spreadsheet</para>

          <para role="TEXT">Downloads the report to your machine as a Microsoft Excel
          compatible file.</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">You would typically use the <emphasis>CSV</emphasis> or
      <emphasis>Spread</emphasis><emphasis>s</emphasis><emphasis>heet</emphasis>
      format to export the list as a report, so you can use it or customize it
      in your office productivity tools. When you click
      <emphasis>Search</emphasis>, the browser displays the <emphasis>File
      Download</emphasis> prompt, where you can choose to save the file or
      open it. Opening it launches <emphasis>Excel</emphasis> if it is
      available on your workstation.</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Inquiry</title>

    <para role="TEXT">You can check the status, details, and history of transactions. This
    function displays a list of files (that is, the set of events in a
    transaction) that your company has initiated.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Maintenance</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The functions in this part of the menu carry out various maintenance
    tasks.</para>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Set Entity</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Only present if your company has entities. Assign an entity to a
      file (that is, the set of transactions on one trade) that currently has
      none.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of transactions that have no entity
      assigned. Click in the <emphasis>System Id</emphasis> column to open a
      form where you can assign an entity. All transactions of the selected
      file are updated.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">No particular permissions are needed for this action.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Set Reference</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Only present if your company has customer references.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of transactions that have no
      reference assigned. Click in the <emphasis>System Id</emphasis> column
      to open a form where you can assign a reference. All transactions of the
      selected file are updated.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">No particular permissions are needed for this action.</para>
    </section>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Unsigned</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Delete Draft or Unsigned transactions that are out of date and are
      never submitted.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">This function displays a list of Draft or Unsigned
      transactions.</para>

      <para role="TEXT">Click rows to select them (click anywhere in the row – it becomes
      highlighted), then click <emphasis>Delete</emphasis> selected
      transactions at the end of the list to delete them. The system will
      check that you have sufficient authorization.</para>

      <caution>
        <para role="TEXT"><emphasis></emphasis>Deleted records are physically removed from
        the system. This should therefore be done with great care!</para>
      </caution>
    </section>
  </section>
</chapter>
