<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter condition="TITLE=Customer RelationShip Management;PERM=view_project;ACCESS=OTH_CRM"
         role="TOPIC">
  <title><xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_Business_R"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> Module</title>

  <para role="TEXT">The <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
  xpointer="ent_Business_R" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />
  module constitutes the client side of the Customer Relationship Management
  (CRM) features available in <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
  xpointer="ent_appli" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />. It gives
  you an electronic channel of communication with the Trade Services team of
  all the banks your company is entitled to liaise with through the
  portal.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">This module is primarily for non-transactional requests
  (for transactions, the appropriate Product module and function should rather
  be used), and typically provides a way for you to submit your questions such
  as requests for quotes on specific services to a bank's trade team.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">The organisation of this simple knowledge base is similar
  to a database of Frequently Asked Questions. You have access to domains
  representing each relationship your company has with banks within
  <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
  xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />. These contain folders, which
  in turn contain topics with sets of questions and answers.</para>

  <para role="TEXT"><informalexample>
      <para role="TEXT">For example, imagine that your company (whose abbreviated name is
      <literal moreinfo="none">Company1</literal>) has signed up with two
      banks ( <literal moreinfo="none">Bank1</literal> and <literal
      moreinfo="none">Bank2</literal> ) of one banking group (<literal
      moreinfo="none">BankGroup</literal>) for access to <xi:include
      href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_appli"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />. You therefore have access
      to three domains - for communicating with these two branches and the
      higher entity represented by the bank group itself.</para>
    </informalexample></para>

  <para role="TEXT">Therefore, when you access the initial Business Requests
  screen, you are presented with a list of all the domains your company has
  accessed to. In the situation described here, three domains appear: <literal
  moreinfo="none">Bank1 - Company1</literal>, <literal moreinfo="none">Bank2 -
  Company1</literal> and <literal moreinfo="none">BankGroup -
  Company1</literal>.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">Within each domain, folders set up by the branch are
  available to you to organise your questions and answers. A typical folder
  could for instance be called <literal moreinfo="none">Importer
  Area</literal>, to address concerns specific to importers. One level deeper,
  the topics organise the information within one folder, and each of them
  contains a set of questions and answers.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">It is up to the bank to create and organise the folders
  and topics. As a user at a client company, you can browse or search through
  the existing folders and topics, and submit new questions which will
  immediately become visible to the users at the appropriate bank.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Using CRM</title>

    <para role="TEXT">When you click <guimenuitem>Business Requests</guimenuitem>, you are
    presented with a list of domains available to your company. Click the one
    for the bank you want to send a question to.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Alternatively you can click <guilabel>Search</guilabel> to search
    for questions containing a given text, or <guilabel>List
    Unanswered</guilabel> for a list of all questions that users at your
    company have submitted but that have not yet been answered. These two
    functions are available on every page in <xi:include
    href="../entities_en.xml" xpointer="ent_CRM"
    xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" />.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">No function in <xi:include href="../entities_en.xml"
    xpointer="ent_CRM" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" /> enables
    you to see questions submitted from other client companies.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Having selected a domain, you then get a list of folders in that
    domain. If you get <literal>Sorry, there are currently no available
    folders for this domain</literal>, it means the bank has not yet created
    any. It is up to the bank to create folders and topics.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Click a folder in the list to get a tree view showing the topics in
    that folder, and the questions within the topics. Each question is
    followed by a number showing how many answers the bank has posted for it.
    Click a question in the tree view to see the full question and its
    answers.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Alternatively, click a topic in the tree view to get a tree view
    showing just that topic and the questions within it. From this
    single-topic view (and from no other) you get an additional function
    <guilabel>Add New Question</guilabel>. To submit a question to the bank,
    click this link, type your question, and click
    <guilabel>Save</guilabel>.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">Your question is immediately added to the database and so is
    accessible to users both at the bank and at your company. It is also
    brought to the attention of the users at the bank by appearing in the list
    of Trade Recent Requests on their home pages</para>

    <para role="TEXT">At the top of each page in your tree view is a toolbar (sometimes
    called a breadcrumb trail) showing where in the tree you currently are.
    You can move back up the tree by clicking in this toolbar.</para>
  </section>
</chapter>
