<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.3/docbookx.dtd">
<chapter>
  <title>About Opics Portal</title>

  <para role="TEXT">This chapter introduces the Misys Opics Portal and explains its
  significance to its customers.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">Opics Portal offers a key delivery channel for corporate customers to
  quickly and easily manage their global trading activities online. This
  delivery channel provides the opportunity to take advantage of an extensive
  worldwide network of international branches and correspondent banks to speed
  the handling of their trade transactions around the globe.</para>

  <para role="TEXT">Using a comprehensive web-based interface, the customers can process
  and review their transactions. They can submit business requests and also
  browse through analysis or information pertaining to their financial
  transactions.</para>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Managing Customer Static Data</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Opics Plus customers are defined as global static data, that is, all
    customers are available to trade with all legal entities which can be
    banks or branches.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The portal also defines customer but requires mapping of customers
    to the legal entities. Each mapping in the portal requires a reference
    code to be created that can be fed to the back-end system.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">The customers are not entered automatically into the portal.
    Communication between Opics Plus and Opics Portal require a dual key
    method of entry for a manual setup. Alternatively, it is also entered
    using two different interfaces from the bank’s ERM/CRM system.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>End User-Management</title>

    <para role="TEXT">Opics Portal users are designated with one or more customers
    associated with one or more banks or branches. Using the portal, a single
    end user can initiate transactions on behalf of multiple customers and
    banks or branches.</para>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Product Management</title>

    <section role="ITEM">
      <title>Global Product List</title>

      <para role="TEXT">Opics Portal manages the list of products available for trade.
      Currently, it provides the following modules of Opics Plus:</para>

      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Foreign Exchange</para>

          <para role="TEXT">That includes Spot, Forward, Swap, Delivery Option, Order,
          Split, Extend, Uptake, and Option Takedown</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Term Deposits and Loans</para>

          <para role="TEXT">That includes Trade, Rollover, Reversal</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Foreign Exchange Orders</para>
        </listitem>

        <listitem>
          <para role="TEXT">Fund Transfers</para>
        </listitem>
      </itemizedlist>

      <para role="TEXT">The portal also allows you to select and restrict the products
      available for trading.</para>
    </section>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Customer Accounts</title>

    <para role="TEXT">The following Call Account information of customers is displayed in
    the Portal.</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Name</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Customer</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Description</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Currency</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Current Interest Rate</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Status (Open/Closed)</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Last Statement Date</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para role="TEXT">Last Statement Closing Balance</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </section>

  <section role="ITEM">
    <title>Incomplete Forms &amp; Error Handling</title>

    <para role="TEXT">If the user submits an incomplete form in the portal, the
    transaction request is not processed and the missing data is highlighted
    by an indicator or an error message.</para>

    <para role="TEXT">When a transaction is submitted, the user must provide all required
    fields in the corresponding form. On successfully processing, a message is
    displayed for confirmation.</para>
  </section>
</chapter>
